<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Isaiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/isaiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Isaiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/isaiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 49:8-15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah49_8-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah49_8-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Thus says the Lord:&#xA;In a time of favor I answer you,&#xA;on the day of salvation I help you;&#xA;And I have kept you and given you as a covenant to the people,&#xA;To restore the land and allot the desolate heritages,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Saying to the prisoners: Come out!&#xA;To those in darkness: Show yourselves!&#xA;Along the ways they shall find pasture,&#xA;on every bare height shall their pastures be.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; They shall not hunger or thirst,&#xA;nor shall the scorching wind or the sun strike them;&#xA;For he who pities them leads them&#xA;and guides them beside springs of water.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; I will cut a road through all my mountains,&#xA;and make my highways level.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; See, some shall come from afar,&#xA;others from the north and the west,&#xA;and some from the land of Syene.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Sing out, O heavens, and rejoice, O earth,&#xA;break forth into song, you mountains.&#xA;For the Lord comforts his people&#xA;and shows mercy to his afflicted.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; But Zion said, “The Lord has forsaken me;&#xA;my Lord has forgotten me.”&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; Can a mother forget her infant,&#xA;be without tenderness for the child of her womb?&#xA;Even should she forget,&#xA;I will never forget you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 65:17-21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah65_17-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah65_17-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17.&lt;/strong&gt; Lo, I am about to create new heavens and a new earth; The things of the past shall not be remembered or come to mind.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18.&lt;/strong&gt; Instead, there shall always be rejoicing and happiness in what I create; For I create Jerusalem to be a joy and its people to be a delight.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19.&lt;/strong&gt; I will rejoice in Jerusalem and exult in my people. No longer shall the sound of weeping be heard there, or the sound of crying;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20.&lt;/strong&gt; No longer shall there be in it an infant who lives but a few days, or an old man who does not round out his full lifetime; He dies a mere youth who reaches but a hundred years, and he who fails of a hundred shall be thought accursed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21.&lt;/strong&gt; They shall live in the houses they build, and eat the fruit of the vineyards they plant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 1:10,16-20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Hear the word of the LORD, ye rulers of Sodom; give ear unto the law of our God, ye people of Gomorrah.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; Wash you, make you clean; put away the evil of your doings from before mine eyes; cease to do evil;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Learn to do well; seek judgment, relieve the oppressed, judge the fatherless, plead for the widow.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; If ye be willing and obedient, ye shall eat the good of the land:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But if ye refuse and rebel, ye shall be devoured with the sword: for the mouth of the LORD hath spoken it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
