<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Isaiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/isaiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Isaiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/isaiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 49:8-15</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah49_8-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah49_8-15/</guid>
      <description>Reading 8 Thus says the Lord: In a time of favor I answer you, on the day of salvation I help you; And I have kept you and given you as a covenant to the people, To restore the land and allot the desolate heritages, 9 Saying to the prisoners: Come out! To those in darkness: Show yourselves! Along the ways they shall find pasture, on every bare height shall their pastures be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 65:17-21</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah65_17-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah65_17-21/</guid>
      <description>Reading 17. Lo, I am about to create new heavens and a new earth; The things of the past shall not be remembered or come to mind. 18. Instead, there shall always be rejoicing and happiness in what I create; For I create Jerusalem to be a joy and its people to be a delight. 19. I will rejoice in Jerusalem and exult in my people. No longer shall the sound of weeping be heard there, or the sound of crying; 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 1:10,16-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</guid>
      <description>10 Hear the word of the LORD, ye rulers of Sodom; give ear unto the law of our God, ye people of Gomorrah.
16 Wash you, make you clean; put away the evil of your doings from before mine eyes; cease to do evil; 17 Learn to do well; seek judgment, relieve the oppressed, judge the fatherless, plead for the widow. 18 Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
