<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/john/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:45:07 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>John 11:45-56</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john11_45-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:45:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john11_45-56/</guid>
      <description>Reading 45 Many therefore of the Jews, who were come to Mary and Martha and had seen the things that Jesus did, believed in him.
46 But some of them went to the Pharisees and told them the things that Jesus had done.
47 The chief priests, therefore, and the Pharisees gathered a council and said: What do we, for this man doth many miracles?
48 If we let him alone so, all will believe in him; and the Romans will come, and take away our place and nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 10:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john10_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john10_31-42/</guid>
      <description>Reading 31 The Jews then took up stones to stone him.
32 Jesus answered them: Many good works I have shewed you from my Father. For which of those works do you stone me?
33 The Jews answered him: For a good work we stone thee not, but for blasphemy: and because that thou, being a man, makest thyself God.
34 Jesus answered them: Is it not written in your law: I said, you are gods?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:51-59</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_51-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_51-59/</guid>
      <description>Reading 51 Amen, amen, I say to you: If any man keep my word, he shall not see death for ever.
52 The Jews therefore said: Now we know that thou hast a devil. Abraham is dead, and the prophets: and thou sayest: If any man keep my word, he shall not taste death for ever.
53 Art thou greater than our father Abraham who is dead? And the prophets are dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:05:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_31-42/</guid>
      <description>Reading 31 Then Jesus said to those Jews, who believed him: If you continue in my word, you shall be my disciples indeed.
32 And you shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.
33 They answered him: We are the seed of Abraham, and we have never been slaves to any man: how sayest thou: You shall be free?
34 Jesus answered them: Amen, amen I say unto you: that whosoever committeth sin, is the servant of sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:1-11</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_1-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:09:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_1-11/</guid>
      <description>Reading 1 And Jesus went unto mount Olivet.
2 And early in the morning he came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and sitting down, he taught them.
3 And the scribes and the Pharisees bring unto him a woman taken in adultery; and when they had set her in the midst,
4 They say unto him: Master, this woman was taken in adultery, in the very act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 7:40-53</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john740-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john740-53/</guid>
      <description>Reading 40 Of that multitude therefore, when they had heard these words of his, some said: This is the prophet indeed. 41 Others said: This is the Christ. But some said: Doth the Christ come out of Galilee? 42 Doth not the scripture say: That Christ cometh of the seed of David, and from Bethlehem the town where David was? 43 So there arose a dissension among the people because of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 7:2,10,25-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:01:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</guid>
      <description>Reading 1 After these things Jesus walked in Galilee; for he would not walk in Judea, because the Jews sought to kill him. 2 Now the Jews&#39; feast of tabernacles was at hand. 10 But when his brethren were gone up, then went he also up unto the feast, not openly, but as it were in secret. 25 Then said some of them of Jerusalem, Is not this he, whom they seek to kill?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 15:12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john15_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:46:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john15_12-17/</guid>
      <description>Reading 12 This is my commandment, That you love one another, as I have loved you. 13 Greater love than this no man hath, that a man lay down his life for his friends. 14 You are my friends, if you do the things that I command you. 15 I will not now call you servants: for the servant knoweth not what his lord doth. But I have called you friends: because all things whatsoever I have heard of my Father, I have made known to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 5:17-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john5_17-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john5_17-30/</guid>
      <description>Reading 17 But Jesus answered them, &amp;ldquo;My Father is at work until now, so I am at work.&amp;rdquo; 18 For this reason the Jews tried all the more to kill him, because he not only broke the sabbath but he also called God his own father, making himself equal to God. 19 Jesus answered and said to them, &amp;ldquo;Amen, amen, I say to you, the Son cannot do anything on his own, but only what he sees the Father doing; for what he does, the Son will do also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 4:43-54</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john4_43-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john4_43-54/</guid>
      <description>Reading 43. At that time Jesus left [Samaria] for Galilee. 44. For Jesus himself testified that a prophet has no honor in his native place. 45. When he came into Galilee, the Galileans welcomed him, since they had seen all he had done in Jerusalem at the feast; for they themselves had gone to the feast. &amp;hellip; 54. Now this was the second sign Jesus did when he came to Galilee from Judea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>13 And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.
14 And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: 15 And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; 16 And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
