<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Genesis on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/genesis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Genesis on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:40:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/genesis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 17:3-9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis17_3-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:40:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis17_3-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Abram fell flat on his face.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And God said to him: I am, and my covenant is with thee, and thou shalt be a father of many nations.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Neither shall thy name be called any more Abram: but thou shalt be called Abraham: because I have made thee a father of many nations.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make thee increase exceedingly, and I will make nations of thee, and kings shall come out of thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And I will establish my covenant between me and thee, and between thy seed after thee in their generations, by a perpetual covenant: to be a God to thee, and to thy seed after thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And I will give to thee, and to thy seed, the land of thy sojournment, all the land of Chanaan, for a perpetual possession, and I will be their God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Again God said to Abraham: And thou therefore shalt keep my covenant, and thy seed after thee in their generations .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-2,9a-10,13-15,18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis22_1-2_9a_10-13_15-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:56:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis22_1-2_9a_10-13_15-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;feast-day&#34;&gt;Feast Day&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said to him: Abraham, Abraham. And he answered: Here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; He said to him: Take thy only begotten son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and go into the land of vision: and there thou shalt offer him for an holocaust upon one of the mountains which I will shew thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9a&lt;/strong&gt; And they came to the place which God had shewn him,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; where he built an altar, and laid the wood in order upon it: and when he had bound Isaac his son, he laid him on the altar upon the pile of wood.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; And behold an angel of the Lord from heaven called to him, saying: Abraham, Abraham. And he answered: Here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And he said to him: Lay not thy hand upon the boy, neither do thou any thing to him: now I know that thou fearest God, and hast not spared thy only begotten son for my sake.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham lifted up his eyes, and saw behind his back a ram amongst the briers sticking fast by the horns, which he took and offered for a holocaust instead of his son.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And the angel of the Lord called to Abraham a second time from heaven, saying:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; By my own self have I sworn, saith the Lord: because thou hast done this thing, and hast not spared thy only begotten son for my sake:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; I will bless thee, and I will multiply thy seed as the stars of heaven, and as the sand that is by the sea shore; thy seed shall possess the gates of their enemies.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; And in thy seed shall all the nations of the earth be blessed, because thou hast obeyed my voice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 3:9-15, 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis3_9-15_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 18:36:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis3_9-15_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;###Feast Day&#xA;The Memorial of The Blessed Virgin Mary, Mother of the Church, which is observed during the Tenth Week in Ordinary Time&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;genesis-39-15-20&#34;&gt;Genesis 3:9-15, 20&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9.&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord God called Adam, and said to him: Where art thou?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10.&lt;/strong&gt; And he said: I heard thy voice in paradise; and I was afraid, because I was naked, and I hid myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11.&lt;/strong&gt; And he said to him: And who hath told thee that thou wast naked, but that thou hast eaten of the tree whereof I commanded thee that thou shouldst not eat?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 37:3-28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis37_3-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/genesis37_3-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Now Israel loved Joseph more than all his children, because he was the son of his old age: and he made him a coat of many colours.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And when his brethren saw that their father loved him more than all his brethren, they hated him, and could not speak peaceably unto him.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And his brethren went to feed their father’s flock in Shechem.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13a&lt;/strong&gt; And Israel said unto Joseph, Do not thy brethren feed the flock in Shechem? come, and I will send thee unto them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/gen22_1-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/gen22_1-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said unto him, Abraham: and he said, Behold, here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Take now thy son, thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and get thee into the land of Moriah; and offer him there for a burnt offering upon one of the mountains which I will tell thee of.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And they came to the place which God had told him of; and Abraham built an altar there, and laid the wood in order, and bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the altar upon the wood.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
