<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sunday Reading 3-3-2024 on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/sunday-reading-3-3-2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sunday Reading 3-3-2024 on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/sunday-reading-3-3-2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>13 And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.
14 And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: 15 And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; 16 And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians 1:22-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:10:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</guid>
      <description>22 For the Jews require a sign, and the Greeks seek after wisdom: 23 But we preach Christ crucified, unto the Jews a stumblingblock, and unto the Greeks foolishness; 24 But unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks, Christ the power of God, and the wisdom of God. 25 Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men【34†source】.
ChatGPT Response Here is the image inspired by 1 Corinthians 1:22-25, capturing the contrast between human wisdom and divine wisdom, with a focus on the symbolic power of the cross as the unifying element of God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom over human understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus 20:1-3,7-8,12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</guid>
      <description>1 And God spake all these words, saying, 2 I am the LORD thy God, which have brought thee out of the land of Egypt, out of the house of bondage. 3 Thou shalt have no other gods before me.
7 Thou shalt not take the name of the LORD thy God in vain; for the LORD will not hold him guiltless that taketh his name in vain. 8 Remember the sabbath day, to keep it holy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
