<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>43 Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.
44 But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;
45 That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 26:16-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:36:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</guid>
      <description>16 This day the LORD thy God hath commanded thee to do these statutes and judgments: thou shalt therefore keep and do them with all thine heart, and with all thy soul.
17 Thou hast avouched the LORD this day to be thy God, and to walk in his ways, and to keep his statutes, and his commandments, and his judgments, and to hearken unto his voice:
18 And the LORD hath avouched thee this day to be his peculiar people, as he hath promised thee, and that thou shouldest keep all his commandments;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
My name is Norm. Thank you for visiting!
The images used on this site are generated using OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT. The verses are from the dail Mass readings so we will make our journy through the Bible in 2 years.
All images on this site come from ChatGPT unless specified otherwise. They are also free for you to use, though attribution and a donation would be nice, it is not required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>20 For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.
21 Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: 22 But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>21 But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.
22 All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.
23 Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
