<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Luke 6:36-38</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</guid>
      <description>36 Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful.
37 Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shall be forgiven:
38 Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 9:4-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</guid>
      <description>4b &amp;ldquo;Speak not thou in thine heart, after that the LORD thy God hath cast them out from before thee, saying, For my righteousness the LORD hath brought me in to possess this land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD doth drive them out from before thee.
5 Not for thy righteousness, or for the uprightness of thine heart, dost thou go to possess their land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD thy God doth drive them out from before thee, and that he may perform the word which the LORD sware unto thy fathers, Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark 9:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:56:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</guid>
      <description>2 And after six days Jesus taketh with him Peter, and James, and John, and leadeth them up into a high mountain apart by themselves: and he was transfigured before them.
3 And his raiment became shining, exceeding white as snow; so as no fuller on earth can white them.
4 And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.
5 And Peter answered and said to Jesus, Master, it is good for us to be here: and let us make three tabernacles; one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans 8:31-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/rom8_31-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/rom8_31-34/</guid>
      <description>31 What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?
32 He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?
33 Who shall lay any thing to the charge of God’s elect? It is God that justifieth.
34 Who is he that condemneth? It is Christ that died, yea rather, that is risen again, who is even at the right hand of God, who also maketh intercession for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said unto him, Abraham: and he said, Behold, here I am.
2 And he said, Take now thy son, thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and get thee into the land of Moriah; and offer him there for a burnt offering upon one of the mountains which I will tell thee of.
9 And they came to the place which God had told him of; and Abraham built an altar there, and laid the wood in order, and bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the altar upon the wood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>43 Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.
44 But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;
45 That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 26:16-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:36:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</guid>
      <description>16 This day the LORD thy God hath commanded thee to do these statutes and judgments: thou shalt therefore keep and do them with all thine heart, and with all thy soul.
17 Thou hast avouched the LORD this day to be thy God, and to walk in his ways, and to keep his statutes, and his commandments, and his judgments, and to hearken unto his voice:
18 And the LORD hath avouched thee this day to be his peculiar people, as he hath promised thee, and that thou shouldest keep all his commandments;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
My name is Norm. Thank you for visiting!
The images used on this site are generated using OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT. The verses are from the dail Mass readings so we will make our journy through the Bible in 2 years.
All images on this site come from ChatGPT unless specified otherwise. They are also free for you to use, though attribution and a donation would be nice, it is not required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>20 For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.
21 Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: 22 But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>21 But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.
22 All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.
23 Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
