<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.art/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://matthew419.art/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Luke 14:12-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke14_12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke14_12-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Image: &lt;a href=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/f_webp,q_auto/matthew419/2025/11/luke14_12-14.webp&#34;&gt;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/f_webp,q_auto/matthew419/2025/11/luke14_12-14.webp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Reading — Romans 11:29-36&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;29 For the gifts and calling of God are without repentance.&#xA;30 For as ye in times past have not believed God, yet have now obtained mercy through their unbelief:&#xA;31 Even so have these also now not believed, that through your mercy they also may obtain mercy.&#xA;32 For God hath concluded them all in unbelief, that he might have mercy upon all.&#xA;33 O the depth of the riches both of the wisdom and knowledge of God! how unsearchable are his judgments, and his ways past finding out!&#xA;34 For who hath known the mind of the Lord? or who hath been his counsellor?&#xA;35 Or who hath first given to him, and it shall be recompensed unto him again?&#xA;36 For of him, and through him, and to him, are all things: to whom be glory for ever. Amen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 11:45-56</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john11_45-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:45:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john11_45-56/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; Many therefore of the Jews, who were come to Mary and Martha and had seen the things that Jesus did, believed in him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;46&lt;/strong&gt; But some of them went to the Pharisees and told them the things that Jesus had done.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;47&lt;/strong&gt; The chief priests, therefore, and the Pharisees gathered a council and said: What do we, for this man doth many miracles?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;48&lt;/strong&gt; If we let him alone so, all will believe in him; and the Romans will come, and take away our place and nation.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;49&lt;/strong&gt; But one of them, named Caiphas, being the high priest that year, said to them: You know nothing.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;50&lt;/strong&gt; Neither do you consider that it is expedient for you that one man should die for the people and that the whole nation perish not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; And this he spoke not of himself: but being the high priest of that year, he prophesied that Jesus should die for the nation.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; And not only for the nation, but to gather together in one the children of God that were dispersed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; From that day therefore they devised to put him to death.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54&lt;/strong&gt; Wherefore Jesus walked no more openly among the Jews: but he went into a country near the desert, unto a city that is called Ephrem. And there he abode with his disciples.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;55&lt;/strong&gt; And the pasch of the Jews was at hand: and many from the country went up to Jerusalem, before the pasch, to purify themselves.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;56&lt;/strong&gt; They sought therefore for Jesus; and they discoursed one with another, standing in the temple: What think you that he is not come to the festival day? And the chief priests and Pharisees had given a commandment that, if any man knew where he was, he should tell, that they might apprehend him .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 37:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/ezekiel37_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:41:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/ezekiel37_21-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And thou shalt say to them: Thus saith the Lord God: Behold, I will take of the children of Israel from the midst of the nations whither they are gone: and I will gather them on every side, and will bring them to their own land.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make them one nation in the land on the mountains of Israel, and one king shall be king over them all: and they shall no more be two nations, neither shall they be divided any more into two kingdoms.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Nor shall they be defiled any more with their idols, nor with their abominations, nor with all their iniquities: and I will save them out of all the places in which they have sinned, and I will cleanse them: and they shall be my people, and I will be their God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And my servant David shall be king over them, and they shall have one shepherd: they shall walk in my judgments, and shall keep my commandments, and shall do them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; And they shall dwell in the land which I gave to my servant Jacob, wherein your fathers dwelt, and they shall dwell in it, they and their children, and their children&amp;rsquo;s children, for ever: and David my servant shall be their prince for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make a covenant of peace with them, it shall be an everlasting covenant with them: and I will establish them, and will multiply them, and will set my sanctuary in the midst of them for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And my tabernacle shall be with them: and I will be their God, and they shall be my people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And the nations shall know that I am the Lord the sanctifier of Israel, when my sanctuary shall be in the midst of them for ever .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 10:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john10_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john10_31-42/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews then took up stones to stone him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Many good works I have shewed you from my Father. For which of those works do you stone me?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews answered him: For a good work we stone thee not, but for blasphemy: and because that thou, being a man, makest thyself God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Is it not written in your law: I said, you are gods?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; If he called them gods to whom the word of God was spoken; and the scripture cannot be broken:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Do you say of him whom the Father hath sanctified and sent into the world: Thou blasphemest; because I said: I am the Son of God?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; If I do not the works of my Father, believe me not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; But if I do, though you will not believe me, believe the works: that you may know and believe that the Father is in me and I in the Father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; They sought therefore to take him: and he escaped out of their hands.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; And he went again beyond the Jordan, into that place where John was baptizing first. And there he abode.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; And many resorted to him: and they said: John indeed did no sign.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; But all things whatsoever John said of this man were true. And many believed in him .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 20:10-13</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah20_10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:24:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah20_10-13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; For I heard the reproaches of many, and terror on every side: Persecute him, and let us persecute him: from all the men that were my familiars, and continued at my side: if by any means he may be deceived, and we may prevail against him, and be revenged on him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But the Lord is with me as a strong warrior: therefore they that persecute me shall fall, and shall be weak: they shall be greatly confounded, because they have not understood the everlasting reproach, which never shall be effaced.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And thou, O Lord of hosts, prover of the just, who seest the reins and the heart: let me see, I beseech thee, thy vengeance on them: for to thee I have laid open my cause.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Sing ye to the Lord, praise the Lord: because he hath delivered the soul of the poor out of the hand of the wicked .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:51-59</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_51-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_51-59/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you: If any man keep my word, he shall not see death for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews therefore said: Now we know that thou hast a devil. Abraham is dead, and the prophets: and thou sayest: If any man keep my word, he shall not taste death for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; Art thou greater than our father Abraham who is dead? And the prophets are dead. Whom dost thou make thyself?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered: If I glorify myself, my glory is nothing. It is my Father that glorifieth me, of whom you say that he is your God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;55&lt;/strong&gt; And you have not known him: but I know him. And if I shall say that I know him not, I shall be like to you, a liar. But I do know him and do keep his word.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;56&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham your father rejoiced that he might see my day: he saw it and was glad.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;57&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews therefore said to him: Thou art not yet fifty years old. And hast thou seen Abraham?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;58&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus said to them: Amen, amen, I say to you, before Abraham was made, I AM.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;59&lt;/strong&gt; They took up stones therefore to cast at him. But Jesus hid himself and went out of the temple .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 17:3-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis17_3-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:40:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis17_3-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Abram fell flat on his face.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And God said to him: I am, and my covenant is with thee, and thou shalt be a father of many nations.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Neither shall thy name be called any more Abram: but thou shalt be called Abraham: because I have made thee a father of many nations.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make thee increase exceedingly, and I will make nations of thee, and kings shall come out of thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And I will establish my covenant between me and thee, and between thy seed after thee in their generations, by a perpetual covenant: to be a God to thee, and to thy seed after thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And I will give to thee, and to thy seed, the land of thy sojournment, all the land of Chanaan, for a perpetual possession, and I will be their God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Again God said to Abraham: And thou therefore shalt keep my covenant, and thy seed after thee in their generations .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:05:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_31-42/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; Then Jesus said to those Jews, who believed him: If you continue in my word, you shall be my disciples indeed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; And you shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; They answered him: We are the seed of Abraham, and we have never been slaves to any man: how sayest thou: You shall be free?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Amen, amen I say unto you: that whosoever committeth sin, is the servant of sin.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And the servant abideth not in the house for ever; but the Son abideth for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; If therefore the Son shall make you free, you shall be free indeed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; I know that you are the children of Abraham: but you seek to kill me, because my word hath no place in you.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; I speak that which I have seen with my Father: and you do the things that you have seen with your father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; They answered, and said to him: Abraham is our father. Jesus saith to them: If you be the children of Abraham, do the works of Abraham.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; But now you seek to kill me, a man who have spoken to you the truth, which I have heard of God. This Abraham did not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; You do the works of your father. They said therefore to him: We are not born of fornication; we have one Father, even God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus said to them: If God were your Father, you would indeed love me. For from God I proceeded, and came; for I came not of myself, but he sent me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel3_14 20_91 92_95</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel3_14-20_91-92_95/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel3_14-20_91-92_95/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; Nebuchadnezzar addressing them, said: Is it true, O Sidrach, Misach, and Abdenago, that you do not worship my gods, nor adore the golden statue that I have set up?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; Now therefore if you be ready, at what hour soever you shall hear the sound of the trumpet, flute, harp, sackbut, psaltery, and symphony, and of all kinds of music, prostrate yourselves, and adore the statue that I have made: but if you do not adore, you shall be cast the same hour into the furnace of burning fire: and who is the God that shall deliver you out of my hand?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; Sidrach, Misach, and Abdenago answered and said to king Nebuchadnezzar: We have no occasion to answer thee concerning this matter.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; For behold our God, whom we worship, is able to save us from the furnace of burning fire, and to deliver us out of thy hands, O king.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; But if he will not, be it known to thee, O king, that we will not worship thy gods, nor adore the golden statue which thou hast set up.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Then was Nebuchadnezzar filled with fury: and the countenance of his face was changed against Sidrach, Misach, and Abdenago, and he commanded that the furnace should be heated seven times more than it was wont to be heated.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; And he commanded the strongest men that were in his army, to bind the feet of Sidrach, Misach, and Abdenago, and to cast them into the furnace of burning fire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 1:16-24</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew1_16-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 03:26:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew1_16-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And Jacob begot Joseph the husband of Mary, of whom was born Jesus, who is called Christ.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Now the birth of Jesus Christ was on this wise: When as his mother Mary was espoused to Joseph, before they came together, she was found with child of the Holy Ghost.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Then Joseph her husband, being a just man, and not willing to make her a public example, was minded to put her away privily.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But while he thought on these things, behold, the angel of the Lord appeared unto him in a dream, saying, Joseph, thou son of David, fear not to take unto thee Mary thy wife: for that which is conceived in her is of the Holy Ghost.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And she shall bring forth a son, and thou shalt call his name JESUS: for he shall save his people from their sins.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24a&lt;/strong&gt; Then Joseph being raised from sleep did as the angel of the Lord had bidden him, and took unto him his wife:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel 7:4-5a,12-14a,16</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/2samuel7_4-5_12-14_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 03:20:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/2samuel7_4-5_12-14_16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; But it came to pass that night, that the word of the Lord came to Nathan, saying:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5a&lt;/strong&gt; Go, and say to my servant David, Thus saith the Lord:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And when thy days shall be fulfilled, and thou shalt sleep with thy fathers, I will raise up thy seed after thee, which shall proceed out of thy bowels, and I will establish his kingdom.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; He shall build a house to my name, and I will establish the throne of his kingdom for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14a&lt;/strong&gt; I will be to him a father, and he shall be to me a son.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And thy house shall be faithful, and thy kingdom for ever before thy face, and thy throne shall be established for ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:1-11</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_1-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:09:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_1-11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus went unto mount Olivet.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And early in the morning he came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and sitting down, he taught them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And the scribes and the Pharisees bring unto him a woman taken in adultery; and when they had set her in the midst,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; They say unto him: Master, this woman was taken in adultery, in the very act.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Now Moses in the law commanded us, that such should be stoned. But what sayest thou?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; This they said, tempting him, that they might have to accuse him. But Jesus stooped down, and with his finger wrote on the ground, as though he heard them not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; So when they continued asking him, he lifted up himself, and said unto them: He that is without sin among you, let him first cast a stone at her.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And again he stooped down, and wrote on the ground.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And they which heard it, being convicted by their own conscience, went out one by one, beginning at the eldest, even unto the last: and Jesus was left alone, and the woman standing in the midst.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; When Jesus had lifted up himself, and saw none but the woman, he said unto her: Woman, where are those thine accusers? hath no man condemned thee?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; She said, No man, Lord. And Jesus said unto her: Neither do I condemn thee: go, and sin no more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel 13:1-9,5-17, 19-30, 33-62</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel13_1-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:55:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel13_1-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; In Babylon there lived a man named Joakim,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; who married a woman named Susanna, the daughter of Hilkiah, a very beautiful woman and one who feared the Lord.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Her parents were righteous and had instructed their daughter according to the law of Moses.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; Joakim was very rich; he had a garden near his house, and the Jews came to him because he was the most honored of them all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-2,9a-10,13-15,18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis22_1-2_9a_10-13_15-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:56:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis22_1-2_9a_10-13_15-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;feast-day&#34;&gt;Feast Day&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said to him: Abraham, Abraham. And he answered: Here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; He said to him: Take thy only begotten son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and go into the land of vision: and there thou shalt offer him for an holocaust upon one of the mountains which I will shew thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9a&lt;/strong&gt; And they came to the place which God had shewn him,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; where he built an altar, and laid the wood in order upon it: and when he had bound Isaac his son, he laid him on the altar upon the pile of wood.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; And behold an angel of the Lord from heaven called to him, saying: Abraham, Abraham. And he answered: Here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And he said to him: Lay not thy hand upon the boy, neither do thou any thing to him: now I know that thou fearest God, and hast not spared thy only begotten son for my sake.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham lifted up his eyes, and saw behind his back a ram amongst the briers sticking fast by the horns, which he took and offered for a holocaust instead of his son.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And the angel of the Lord called to Abraham a second time from heaven, saying:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; By my own self have I sworn, saith the Lord: because thou hast done this thing, and hast not spared thy only begotten son for my sake:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; I will bless thee, and I will multiply thy seed as the stars of heaven, and as the sand that is by the sea shore; thy seed shall possess the gates of their enemies.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; And in thy seed shall all the nations of the earth be blessed, because thou hast obeyed my voice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 7:40-53</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john740-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john740-53/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; Of that multitude therefore, when they had heard these words of his, some said: This is the prophet indeed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; Others said: This is the Christ. But some said: Doth the Christ come out of Galilee?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Doth not the scripture say: That Christ cometh of the seed of David, and from Bethlehem the town where David was?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; So there arose a dissension among the people because of him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;44&lt;/strong&gt; And some of them would have apprehended him: but no man laid hands upon him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; The ministers therefore came to the chief priests and the Pharisees. And they said to them: Why have you not brought him?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;46&lt;/strong&gt; The ministers answered: Never did man speak like this man.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;47&lt;/strong&gt; The Pharisees therefore answered them: Are you also seduced?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;48&lt;/strong&gt; Hath any one of the rulers believed in him, or of the Pharisees?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;49&lt;/strong&gt; But this multitude, that knoweth not the law, are accursed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;50&lt;/strong&gt; Nicodemus, he that came to him by night, who was one of them, saith to them:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; Doth our law judge any man, unless it first hear him, and know what he doth?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; They answered, and said to him: Art thou also a Galilean? Search the scriptures, and see that out of Galilee a prophet riseth not.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; And every man returned to his own house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 11:18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah11_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:26:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah11_18-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord hath given me knowledge of it, and I know it: then thou showedst me their doings.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; But I was like a meek lamb that is carried to be sacrificed: and I knew not that they had devised devices against me, saying: Let us put wood in his bread, and cut him off from the land of the living, and let his name be remembered no more.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But, O Lord of hosts, that judgest righteously, that triest the reins and the hearts, let me see thy vengeance on them: for to thee have I revealed my cause.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 7:2,10,25-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:01:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; After these things Jesus walked in Galilee; for he would not walk in Judea, because the Jews sought to kill him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Now the Jews&amp;rsquo; feast of tabernacles was at hand.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; But when his brethren were gone up, then went he also up unto the feast, not openly, but as it were in secret.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Then said some of them of Jerusalem, Is not this he, whom they seek to kill?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And, lo, he speaketh boldly, and they say nothing unto him. Do the rulers know indeed that this is the very Christ?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Howbeit we know this man whence he is: but when Christ cometh, no man knoweth whence he is.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Then cried Jesus in the temple as he taught, saying, Ye both know me, and ye know whence I am: and I am not come of myself, but he that sent me is true, whom ye know not.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; But I know him: for I am from him, and he hath sent me.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; Then they sought to take him: but no man laid hands on him, because his hour was not yet come.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisdom 2:1a,12-22</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/wisdom2_1a_12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 01:52:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/wisdom2_1a_12-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1a&lt;/strong&gt; For they have said, reasoning with themselves, but not right: The time of our life is short and tedious, and in the end of a man there is no remedy, and no man hath been known to have returned from hell.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore let us enjoy the good things that are present, and let us speedily use the creatures like as in youth.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Let us fill ourselves with costly wine and ointments: and let no flower of the spring pass by us.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; Let us crown ourselves with rosebuds before they be withered.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; Let none of us go without his part of our voluptuousness: let us leave tokens of our joyfulness in every place: for this is our portion, and our lot is this.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; Let us oppress the poor just man, and not spare the widow, nor reverence the ancient gray hairs of the aged.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Let our strength be the law of justice: for that which is feeble, is found to be nothing worth.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Let us therefore lie in wait for the just, because he is not for our turn, and he is contrary to our doings, and upbraideth us with transgressions of the law, and divulgeth against us the sins of our way of life.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; He boasteth that he hath the knowledge of God, and calleth himself the son of God.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; He was made to reprove our thoughts.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; He is grievous unto us, even to behold: for his life is not like other men&amp;rsquo;s, his ways are of another fashion.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; We are esteemed by him as triflers, and he abstaineth from our ways as from filthiness, and he preferreth the latter end of the just, and glorieth that he is in the company of God.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 15:12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john15_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:46:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john15_12-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; This is my commandment, That you love one another, as I have loved you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Greater love than this no man hath, that a man lay down his life for his friends.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; You are my friends, if you do the things that I command you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; I will not now call you servants: for the servant knoweth not what his lord doth. But I have called you friends: because all things whatsoever I have heard of my Father, I have made known to you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; You have not chosen me: but I have chosen you; and have appointed you, that you should go, and should bring forth fruit; and your fruit should remain: that whatsoever you shall ask of the Father in my name, he may give it you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; These things I command you, that you love one another.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exodus 32:7-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/exodus32_7-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:39:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/exodus32_7-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying: Go, get thee down: thy people, which thou broughtest out of the land of Egypt, have sinned.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; They have quickly strayed from the way which I commanded them: they have made to themselves a molten calf, and have adored it, and sacrificing victims to it, have said: These are thy gods, O Israel, that have brought thee out of the land of Egypt.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And again the Lord said to Moses: I see that this people is stiffnecked:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Let me alone, that my wrath may be kindled against them, and that I may destroy them, and I will make of thee a great nation.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But Moses besought the Lord his God, saying: Why, O Lord, is thy indignation enkindled against thy people, whom thou hast brought out of the land of Egypt, with great power, and with a mighty hand?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; Let not the Egyptians say, I beseech thee: He craftily brought them out, that he might kill them in the mountains, and destroy them from the earth: let thy anger cease, and be appeased upon the wickedness of thy people.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Remember Abraham, Isaac, and Israel, thy servants, to whom thou sworest by thy own self, saying: I will multiply your seed as the stars of heaven: and this whole land that I have spoken of, I will give to your seed, and they shall possess it for ever.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord was appeased from doing the evil which he had spoken against his people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 5:17-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john5_17-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john5_17-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus answered them, &amp;ldquo;My Father is at work until now, so I am at work.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; For this reason the Jews tried all the more to kill him, because he not only broke the sabbath but he also called God his own father, making himself equal to God.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered and said to them, &amp;ldquo;Amen, amen, I say to you, the Son cannot do anything on his own, but only what he sees the Father doing; for what he does, the Son will do also.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; For the Father loves the Son and shows him everything that he himself does, and he will show him greater works than these, so that you may be amazed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; For just as the Father raises the dead and gives life, so also does the Son give life to whomever he wishes.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; Nor does the Father judge anyone, but he has given all judgment to the Son,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; so that all may honor the Son just as they honor the Father. Whoever does not honor the Son does not honor the Father who sent him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you, whoever hears my word and believes in the one who sent me has eternal life and will not come to condemnation, but has passed from death to life.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you, the hour is coming and is now here when the dead will hear the voice of the Son of God, and those who hear will live.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; For just as the Father has life in himself, so also he gave to his Son the possession of life in himself.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And he gave him power to exercise judgment, because he is the Son of Man.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Do not be amazed at this, because the hour is coming in which all who are in the tombs will hear his voice&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; and will come out, those who have done good deeds to the resurrection of life, but those who have done wicked deeds to the resurrection of condemnation.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I cannot do anything on my own; I judge as I hear, and my judgment is just, because I do not seek my own will but the will of the one who sent me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 49:8-15</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah49_8-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah49_8-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Thus says the Lord:&#xA;In a time of favor I answer you,&#xA;on the day of salvation I help you;&#xA;And I have kept you and given you as a covenant to the people,&#xA;To restore the land and allot the desolate heritages,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Saying to the prisoners: Come out!&#xA;To those in darkness: Show yourselves!&#xA;Along the ways they shall find pasture,&#xA;on every bare height shall their pastures be.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; They shall not hunger or thirst,&#xA;nor shall the scorching wind or the sun strike them;&#xA;For he who pities them leads them&#xA;and guides them beside springs of water.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; I will cut a road through all my mountains,&#xA;and make my highways level.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; See, some shall come from afar,&#xA;others from the north and the west,&#xA;and some from the land of Syene.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Sing out, O heavens, and rejoice, O earth,&#xA;break forth into song, you mountains.&#xA;For the Lord comforts his people&#xA;and shows mercy to his afflicted.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; But Zion said, “The Lord has forsaken me;&#xA;my Lord has forgotten me.”&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; Can a mother forget her infant,&#xA;be without tenderness for the child of her womb?&#xA;Even should she forget,&#xA;I will never forget you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 65:17-21</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah65_17-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah65_17-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17.&lt;/strong&gt; Lo, I am about to create new heavens and a new earth; The things of the past shall not be remembered or come to mind.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18.&lt;/strong&gt; Instead, there shall always be rejoicing and happiness in what I create; For I create Jerusalem to be a joy and its people to be a delight.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19.&lt;/strong&gt; I will rejoice in Jerusalem and exult in my people. No longer shall the sound of weeping be heard there, or the sound of crying;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20.&lt;/strong&gt; No longer shall there be in it an infant who lives but a few days, or an old man who does not round out his full lifetime; He dies a mere youth who reaches but a hundred years, and he who fails of a hundred shall be thought accursed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21.&lt;/strong&gt; They shall live in the houses they build, and eat the fruit of the vineyards they plant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 4:43-54</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john4_43-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john4_43-54/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;43.&lt;/strong&gt; At that time Jesus left [Samaria] for Galilee.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;44.&lt;/strong&gt; For Jesus himself testified that a prophet has no honor in his native place.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;45.&lt;/strong&gt; When he came into Galilee, the Galileans welcomed him, since they had seen all he had done in Jerusalem at the feast; for they themselves had gone to the feast.&#xA;&amp;hellip;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54.&lt;/strong&gt; Now this was the second sign Jesus did when he came to Galilee from Judea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 3:9-15, 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis3_9-15_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 18:36:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis3_9-15_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;###Feast Day&#xA;The Memorial of The Blessed Virgin Mary, Mother of the Church, which is observed during the Tenth Week in Ordinary Time&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;genesis-39-15-20&#34;&gt;Genesis 3:9-15, 20&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9.&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord God called Adam, and said to him: Where art thou?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10.&lt;/strong&gt; And he said: I heard thy voice in paradise; and I was afraid, because I was naked, and I hid myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11.&lt;/strong&gt; And he said to him: And who hath told thee that thou wast naked, but that thou hast eaten of the tree whereof I commanded thee that thou shouldst not eat?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 25:31-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew25_31-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:55:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew25_31-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matthew 25:31-46&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;When the Son of man shall come in his majesty, and all the angels with him, then shall he sit upon the seat of his majesty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32.&lt;/strong&gt; And all nations shall be gathered together before him: and he shall separate them one from another, as the shepherd separateth the sheep from the goats:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33.&lt;/strong&gt; And he shall set the sheep on his right hand, but the goats on his left.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus 19:1 2, 11-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/leviticus19_1-2_11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:54:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/leviticus19_1-2_11-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leviticus 19:1-2, 11-18&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Speak to all the congregation of the children of Israel. And thou shalt say to them: Be ye holy, because I the Lord your God am holy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11.&lt;/strong&gt; You shall not steal. You shall not lie: neither shall any man deceive his neighbour.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12.&lt;/strong&gt; Thou shalt not swear falsely by my name, nor profane the name of thy God. I am the Lord.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 18:9-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke18_9-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke18_9-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And he spake this parable unto certain which trusted in themselves that they were righteous, and despised others:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Two men went up into the temple to pray; the one a Pharisee, and the other a publican.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; The Pharisee stood and prayed thus with himself, God, I thank thee, that I am not as other men are, extortioners, unjust, adulterers, or even as this publican.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; I fast twice in the week, I give tithes of all that I possess.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And the publican, standing afar off, would not lift up so much as his eyes unto heaven, but smote upon his breast, saying, God be merciful to me a sinner.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; I tell you, this man went down to his house justified rather than the other: for every one that exalteth himself shall be abased.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 6:1-6</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea6_1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea6_1-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Come, and let us return unto the LORD: for he hath torn, and he will heal us; he hath smitten, and he will bind us up.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; After two days will he revive us: in the third day he will raise us up, and we shall live in his sight.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Then shall we know, if we follow on to know the LORD: his going forth is prepared as the morning; and he shall come unto us as the rain, as the latter and former rain unto the earth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; O Ephraim, what shall I do unto thee? O Judah, what shall I do unto thee? for your goodness is as a morning cloud, and as the early dew it goeth away.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore have I hewed them by the prophets; I have slain them by the words of my mouth: and thy judgments are as the light that goeth forth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; For I desired mercy, and not sacrifice; and the knowledge of God more than burnt offerings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acts 1:12-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/acts112-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/acts112-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;feast-day&#34;&gt;Feast Day&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Memorial of The Blessed Virgin Mary, Mother of the Church, which is observed during the Tenth Week in Ordinary Time&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;acts-112-14&#34;&gt;Acts 1:12-14&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12.&lt;/strong&gt; Then they returned to Jerusalem from the mount that is called Olivet, which is nigh Jerusalem, within a sabbath day&amp;rsquo;s journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13.&lt;/strong&gt; And when they were come in, they went up into an upper room, where abode Peter and John, James and Andrew, Philip and Thomas, Bartholomew and Matthew, James of Alpheus and Simon Zelotes and Jude the brother of James.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark 12:28-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/mark12_28-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:16:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/mark12_28-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And one of the scribes came, and having heard them reasoning together, and perceiving that he had answered them well, asked him, Which is the first commandment of all?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus answered him, The first of all the commandments is, Hear, O Israel; The Lord our God is one Lord:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; And thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy mind, and with all thy strength: this is the first commandment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 14:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea14_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:15:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea14_2-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Take with you words, and turn to the LORD: say unto him, Take away all iniquity, and receive us graciously: so will we render the calves of our lips.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Asshur shall not save us; we will not ride upon horses: neither will we say any more to the work of our hands, Ye are our gods: for in thee the fatherless findeth mercy.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; I will heal their backsliding, I will love them freely: for mine anger is turned away from him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; I will be as the dew unto Israel: he shall grow as the lily, and cast forth his roots as Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; His branches shall spread, and his beauty shall be as the olive tree, and his smell as Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; They that dwell under his shadow shall return; they shall revive as the corn, and grow as the vine: the scent thereof shall be as the wine of Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Ephraim shall say, What have I to do any more with idols? I have heard him, and observed him: I am like a green fir tree. From me is thy fruit found.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Who is wise, and he shall understand these things? prudent, and he shall know them? for the ways of the LORD are right, and the just shall walk in them: but the transgressors shall fall therein.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 7:23-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; But this thing commanded I them, saying, Obey my voice, and I will be your God, and ye shall be my people: and walk ye in all the ways that I have commanded you, that it may be well unto you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But they hearkened not, nor inclined their ear, but walked in the counsels and in the imagination of their evil heart, and went backward, and not forward.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Since the day that your fathers came forth out of the land of Egypt unto this day I have even sent unto you all my servants the prophets, daily rising up early and sending them:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; Yet they hearkened not unto me, nor inclined their ear, but hardened their neck: they did worse than their fathers.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore thou shalt speak all these words unto them; but they will not hearken to thee: thou shalt also call unto them; but they will not answer thee.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; But thou shalt say unto them, This is a nation that obeyeth not the voice of the LORD their God, nor receiveth correction: truth is perished, and is cut off from their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 11:14-23</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke11_14-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke11_14-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;luke-1114-23&#34;&gt;Luke 11:14-23&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And he was casting out a devil, and it was dumb. And it came to pass, when the devil was gone out, the dumb spake; and the people wondered.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; But some of them said, He casteth out devils through Beelzebub the chief of the devils.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And others, tempting him, sought of him a sign from heaven.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; But he, knowing their thoughts, said unto them, Every kingdom divided against itself is brought to desolation; and a house divided against a house falleth.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; If Satan also be divided against himself, how shall his kingdom stand? because ye say that I cast out devils through Beelzebub.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And if I by Beelzebub cast out devils, by whom do your sons cast them out? therefore shall they be your judges.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But if I with the finger of God cast out devils, no doubt the kingdom of God is come upon you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; When a strong man armed keepeth his palace, his goods are in peace:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But when a stronger than he shall come upon him, and overcome him, he taketh from him all his armour wherein he trusted, and divideth his spoils.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; He that is not with me is against me: and he that gathereth not with me scattereth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:17-19</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_17-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:17:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_17-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Think not that I am come to destroy the law, or the prophets: I am not come to destroy, but to fulfil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; For verily I say unto you, Till heaven and earth pass, one jot or one tittle shall in no wise pass from the law, till all be fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Whosoever therefore shall break one of these least commandments, and shall teach men so, he shall be called the least in the kingdom of heaven: but whosoever shall do and teach them, the same shall be called great in the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 4:1,5-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:16:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Now therefore hearken, O Israel, unto the statutes and unto the judgments, which I teach you, for to do them, that ye may live, and go in and possess the land which the LORD God of your fathers giveth you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Behold, I have taught you statutes and judgments, even as the LORD my God commanded me, that ye should do so in the land whither ye go to possess it.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; Keep therefore and do them; for this is your wisdom and your understanding in the sight of the nations, which shall hear all these statutes, and say, Surely this great nation is a wise and understanding people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; For what nation is there so great, who hath God so nigh unto them, as the LORD our God is in all things that we call upon him for?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And what nation is there so great, that hath statutes and judgments so righteous as all this law, which I set before you this day?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Only take heed to thyself, and keep thy soul diligently, lest thou forget the things which thine eyes have seen, and lest they depart from thy heart all the days of thy life: but teach them thy sons, and thy sons&amp;rsquo; sons;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 18:21-35</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew18_21-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:17:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew18_21-35/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; Then came Peter to him, and said, Lord, how oft shall my brother sin against me, and I forgive him? till seven times?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith unto him, I say not unto thee, Until seven times: but, Until seventy times seven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore is the kingdom of heaven likened unto a certain king, which would take account of his servants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had begun to reckon, one was brought unto him, which owed him ten thousand talents.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel 3:25,34-43</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; He answered and said, Lo, I see four men loose, walking in the midst of the fire, and they have no hurt; and the form of the fourth is like the Son of God【9†source】.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; And at the end of the days I Nebuchadnezzar lifted up mine eyes unto heaven, and mine understanding returned unto me, and I blessed the most High, and I praised and honoured him that liveth for ever, whose dominion is an everlasting dominion, and his kingdom is from generation to generation:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And all the inhabitants of the earth are reputed as nothing: and he doeth according to his will in the army of heaven, and among the inhabitants of the earth: and none can stay his hand, or say unto him, What doest thou?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; At the same time my reason returned unto me; and for the glory of my kingdom, mine honour and brightness returned unto me; and my counsellors and my lords sought unto me; and I was established in my kingdom, and excellent majesty was added unto me.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; Now I Nebuchadnezzar praise and extol and honour the King of heaven, all whose works are truth, and his ways judgment: and those that walk in pride he is able to abase.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 4:24-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke4_24-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:48:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke4_24-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Verily I say unto you, No prophet is accepted in his own country.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But I tell you of a truth, many widows were in Israel in the days of Elias, when the heaven was shut up three years and six months, when great famine was throughout all the land; &lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; But unto none of them was Elias sent, save unto Sarepta, a city of Sidon, unto a woman that was a widow.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And many lepers were in Israel in the time of Eliseus the prophet; and none of them was cleansed, saving Naaman the Syrian.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And all they in the synagogue, when they heard these things, were filled with wrath, &lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And rose up, and thrust him out of the city, and led him unto the brow of the hill whereon their city was built, that they might cast him down headlong.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; But he passing through the midst of them went his way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings 5:1-15</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/2kings5_1-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/2kings5_1-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Now Naaman, captain of the host of the king of Syria, was a great man with his master, and honourable, because by him the LORD had given deliverance unto Syria: he was also a mighty man in valour, but he was a leper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And the Syrians had gone out by companies, and had brought away captive out of the land of Israel a little maid; and she waited on Naaman’s wife.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: &lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; &lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians 1:22-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:10:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; For the Jews require a sign, and the Greeks seek after wisdom:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; But we preach Christ crucified, unto the Jews a stumblingblock, and unto the Greeks foolishness;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks, Christ the power of God, and the wisdom of God.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men【34†source】.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;chatgpt-response&#34;&gt;ChatGPT Response&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the image inspired by 1 Corinthians 1:22-25, capturing the contrast between human wisdom and divine wisdom, with a focus on the symbolic power of the cross as the unifying element of God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom over human understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exodus 20:1-3,7-8,12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And God spake all these words, saying,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; I am the LORD thy God, which have brought thee out of the land of Egypt, out of the house of bondage.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Thou shalt have no other gods before me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; Thou shalt not take the name of the LORD thy God in vain; for the LORD will not hold him guiltless that taketh his name in vain.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Remember the sabbath day, to keep it holy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 15:1-3, 11-32</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:24:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Then drew near unto him all the publicans and sinners for to hear him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And the Pharisees and scribes murmured, saying, This man receiveth sinners, and eateth with them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And he spake this parable unto them, saying,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, A certain man had two sons:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And the younger of them said to his father, Father, give me the portion of goods that falleth to me. And he divided unto them his living.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And not many days after the younger son gathered all together, and took his journey into a far country, and there wasted his substance with riotous living.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had spent all, there arose a mighty famine in that land; and he began to be in want.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And he went and joined himself to a citizen of that country; and he sent him into his fields to feed swine.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And he would fain have filled his belly with the husks that the swine did eat: and no man gave unto him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; And when he came to himself, he said, How many hired servants of my father’s have bread enough and to spare, and I perish with hunger!&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; I will arise and go to my father, and will say unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and before thee,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And am no more worthy to be called thy son: make me as one of thy hired servants.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; And he arose, and came to his father. But when he was yet a great way off, his father saw him, and had compassion, and ran, and fell on his neck, and kissed him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And the son said unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and in thy sight, and am no more worthy to be called thy son.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But the father said to his servants, Bring forth the best robe, and put it on him; and put a ring on his hand, and shoes on his feet:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And bring hither the fatted calf, and kill it; and let us eat, and be merry:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; For this my son was dead, and is alive again; he was lost, and is found. And they began to be merry.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Now his elder son was in the field: and as he came and drew nigh to the house, he heard musick and dancing.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And he called one of the servants, and asked what these things meant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, Thy brother is come; and thy father hath killed the fatted calf, because he hath received him safe and sound.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And he was angry, and would not go in: therefore came his father out, and intreated him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And he answering said to his father, Lo, these many years do I serve thee, neither transgressed I at any time thy commandment: and yet thou never gavest me a kid, that I might make merry with my friends:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; But as soon as this thy son was come, which hath devoured thy living with harlots, thou hast killed for him the fatted calf.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, Son, thou art ever with me, and all that I have is thine.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; It was meet that we should make merry, and be glad: for this thy brother was dead, and is alive again; and was lost, and is found.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micah 7:14-15, 18-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:16:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; Feed thy people with thy rod, the flock of thine heritage, which dwell solitarily in the wood, in the midst of Carmel: let them feed in Bashan and Gilead, as in the days of old.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; According to the days of thy coming out of the land of Egypt will I shew unto him marvellous things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Who is a God like unto thee, that pardoneth iniquity, and passeth by the transgression of the remnant of his heritage? he retaineth not his anger for ever, because he delighteth in mercy.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; He will turn again, he will have compassion upon us; he will subdue our iniquities; and thou wilt cast all their sins into the depths of the sea.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; Thou wilt perform the truth to Jacob, and the mercy to Abraham, which thou hast sworn unto our fathers from the days of old.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 21:33-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew21_33-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew21_33-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; Hear another parable: There was a certain householder, which planted a vineyard, and hedged it round about, and digged a winepress in it, and built a tower, and let it out to husbandmen, and went into a far country:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; And when the time of the fruit drew near, he sent his servants to the husbandmen, that they might receive the fruits of it.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And the husbandmen took his servants, and beat one, and killed another, and stoned another.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Again, he sent other servants more than the first: and they did unto them likewise.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; But last of all he sent unto them his son, saying, They will reverence my son.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; But when the husbandmen saw the son, they said among themselves, This is the heir; come, let us kill him, and let us seize on his inheritance.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; And they caught him, and cast him out of the vineyard, and slew him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; When the lord therefore of the vineyard cometh, what will he do unto those husbandmen?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; They say unto him, He will miserably destroy those wicked men, and will let out his vineyard unto other husbandmen, which shall render him the fruits in their seasons.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith unto them, Did ye never read in the scriptures, The stone which the builders rejected, the same is become the head of the corner: this is the Lord’s doing, and it is marvellous in our eyes?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore say I unto you, The kingdom of God shall be taken from you, and given to a nation bringing forth the fruits thereof.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 37:3-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis37_3-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/genesis37_3-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Now Israel loved Joseph more than all his children, because he was the son of his old age: and he made him a coat of many colours.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And when his brethren saw that their father loved him more than all his brethren, they hated him, and could not speak peaceably unto him.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And his brethren went to feed their father’s flock in Shechem.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13a&lt;/strong&gt; And Israel said unto Joseph, Do not thy brethren feed the flock in Shechem? come, and I will send thee unto them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke16_19 31</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke16_19-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:57:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke16_19-31/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; There was a certain rich man, which was clothed in purple and fine linen, and fared sumptuously every day:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; And there was a certain beggar named Lazarus, which was laid at his gate, full of sores,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And desiring to be fed with the crumbs which fell from the rich man&amp;rsquo;s table: moreover the dogs came and licked his sores.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass, that the beggar died, and was carried by the angels into Abraham&amp;rsquo;s bosom: the rich man also died, and was buried;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And in hell he lift up his eyes, being in torments, and seeth Abraham afar off, and Lazarus in his bosom.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And he cried and said, Father Abraham, have mercy on me, and send Lazarus, that he may dip the tip of his finger in water, and cool my tongue; for I am tormented in this flame.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But Abraham said, Son, remember that thou in thy lifetime receivedst thy good things, and likewise Lazarus evil things: but now he is comforted, and thou art tormented.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And beside all this, between us and you there is a great gulf fixed: so that they which would pass from hence to you cannot; neither can they pass to us, that would come from thence.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Then he said, I pray thee therefore, father, that thou wouldest send him to my father&amp;rsquo;s house:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; For I have five brethren; that he may testify unto them, lest they also come into this place of torment.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham saith unto him, They have Moses and the prophets; let them hear them.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Nay, father Abraham: but if one went unto them from the dead, they will repent.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, If they hear not Moses and the prophets, neither will they be persuaded, though one rose from the dead.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah17_5 10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:48:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Thus saith the LORD; Cursed be the man that trusteth in man, and maketh flesh his arm, and whose heart departeth from the LORD.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; For he shall be like the heath in the desert, and shall not see when good cometh; but shall inhabit the parched places in the wilderness, in a salt land and not inhabited.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; Blessed is the man that trusteth in the LORD, and whose hope the LORD is.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; For he shall be as a tree planted by the waters, and that spreadeth out her roots by the river, and shall not see when heat cometh, but her leaf shall be green; and shall not be careful in the year of drought, neither shall cease from yielding fruit.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; The heart is deceitful above all things, and desperately wicked: who can know it?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; I the LORD search the heart, I try the reins, even to give every man according to his ways, and according to the fruit of his doings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 20:17-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew20_17-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew20_17-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus going up to Jerusalem took the twelve disciples apart in the way, and said unto them,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Behold, we go up to Jerusalem; and the Son of man shall be betrayed unto the chief priests and unto the scribes, and they shall condemn him to death,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And shall deliver him to the Gentiles to mock, and to scourge, and to crucify him: and the third day he shall rise again.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; Then came to him the mother of Zebedee&amp;rsquo;s children with her sons, worshipping him, and desiring a certain thing of him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto her, What wilt thou? She saith unto him, Grant that these my two sons may sit, the one on thy right hand, and the other on the left, in thy kingdom.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus answered and said, Ye know not what ye ask. Are ye able to drink of the cup that I shall drink of, and to be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with? They say unto him, We are able.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And he saith unto them, Ye shall drink indeed of my cup, and be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with: but to sit on my right hand, and on my left, is not mine to give, but it shall be given to them for whom it is prepared of my Father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And when the ten heard it, they were moved with indignation against the two brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus called them unto him, and said, Ye know that the princes of the Gentiles exercise dominion over them, and they that are great exercise authority upon them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; But it shall not be so among you: but whosoever will be great among you, let him be your minister;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever will be chief among you, let him be your servant:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Even as the Son of man came not to be ministered unto, but to minister, and to give his life a ransom for many.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah_18_18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Then said they, Come, and let us devise devices against Jeremiah; for the law shall not perish from the priest, nor counsel from the wise, nor the word from the prophet. Come, and let us smite him with the tongue, and let us not give heed to any of his words.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Give heed to me, O LORD, and hearken to the voice of them that contend with me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23:1-12</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew23_1-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew23_1-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Then spake Jesus to the multitude, and to his disciples,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Saying, The scribes and the Pharisees sit in Moses&amp;rsquo; seat:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; All therefore whatsoever they bid you observe, that observe and do; but do not ye after their works: for they say, and do not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; For they bind heavy burdens and grievous to be borne, and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; But all their works they do for to be seen of men: they make broad their phylacteries, and enlarge the borders of their garments,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; And love the uppermost rooms at feasts, and the chief seats in the synagogues,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And greetings in the markets, and to be called of men, Rabbi, Rabbi.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; But be not ye called Rabbi: for one is your Master, even Christ; and all ye are brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And call no man your father upon the earth: for one is your Father, which is in heaven.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Neither be ye called masters: for one is your Master, even Christ.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But he that is greatest among you shall be your servant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever shall exalt himself shall be abased; and he that shall humble himself shall be exalted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 1:10,16-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Hear the word of the LORD, ye rulers of Sodom; give ear unto the law of our God, ye people of Gomorrah.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; Wash you, make you clean; put away the evil of your doings from before mine eyes; cease to do evil;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Learn to do well; seek judgment, relieve the oppressed, judge the fatherless, plead for the widow.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; If ye be willing and obedient, ye shall eat the good of the land:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But if ye refuse and rebel, ye shall be devoured with the sword: for the mouth of the LORD hath spoken it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 6:36-38</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke6_36-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke6_36-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shall be forgiven:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 9:4-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4b&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Speak not thou in thine heart, after that the LORD thy God hath cast them out from before thee, saying, For my righteousness the LORD hath brought me in to possess this land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD doth drive them out from before thee.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Not for thy righteousness, or for the uprightness of thine heart, dost thou go to possess their land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD thy God doth drive them out from before thee, and that he may perform the word which the LORD sware unto thy fathers, Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; Understand therefore, that the LORD thy God giveth thee not this good land to possess it for thy righteousness; for thou art a stiffnecked people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; Remember, and forget not, how thou provokedst the LORD thy God to wrath in the wilderness: from the day that thou didst depart out of the land of Egypt, until ye came unto this place, ye have been rebellious against the LORD.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Also in Horeb ye provoked the LORD to wrath, so that the LORD was angry with you to have destroyed you.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; When I was gone up into the mount to receive the tables of stone, even the tables of the covenant which the LORD made with you, then I abode in the mount forty days and forty nights, I neither did eat bread nor drink water:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; And the LORD delivered unto me two tables of stone written with the finger of God; and on them was written according to all the words, which the LORD spake with you in the mount out of the midst of the fire in the day of the assembly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark 9:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/mark9_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:56:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/mark9_2-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And after six days Jesus taketh with him Peter, and James, and John, and leadeth them up into a high mountain apart by themselves: and he was transfigured before them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And his raiment became shining, exceeding white as snow; so as no fuller on earth can white them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; And Peter answered and said to Jesus, Master, it is good for us to be here: and let us make three tabernacles; one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romans 8:31-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/rom8_31-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/rom8_31-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; Who shall lay any thing to the charge of God’s elect? It is God that justifieth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Who is he that condemneth? It is Christ that died, yea rather, that is risen again, who is even at the right hand of God, who also maketh intercession for us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/gen22_1-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/gen22_1-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said unto him, Abraham: and he said, Behold, here I am.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Take now thy son, thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and get thee into the land of Moriah; and offer him there for a burnt offering upon one of the mountains which I will tell thee of.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And they came to the place which God had told him of; and Abraham built an altar there, and laid the wood in order, and bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the altar upon the wood.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;44&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 26:16-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:36:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; This day the LORD thy God hath commanded thee to do these statutes and judgments: thou shalt therefore keep and do them with all thine heart, and with all thy soul.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Thou hast avouched the LORD this day to be thy God, and to walk in his ways, and to keep his statutes, and his commandments, and his judgments, and to hearken unto his voice:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; And the LORD hath avouched thee this day to be his peculiar people, as he hath promised thee, and that thou shouldest keep all his commandments;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: &lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die? saith the Lord GOD: and not that he should return from his ways, and live?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But when the righteous turneth away from his righteousness, and committeth iniquity, and doeth according to all the abominations that the wicked man doeth, shall he live? All his righteousness that he hath done shall not be mentioned: in his trespass that he hath trespassed, and in his sin that he hath sinned, in them shall he die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Yet ye say, The way of the Lord is not equal. Hear now, O house of Israel; Is not my way equal? are not your ways unequal?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; When a righteous man turneth away from his righteousness, and committeth iniquity, and dieth in them; for his iniquity that he hath done shall he die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Again, when the wicked man turneth away from his wickedness that he hath committed, and doeth that which is lawful and right, he shall save his soul alive.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Because he considereth, and turneth away from all his transgressions that he hath committed, he shall surely live, he shall not die.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
