<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezekiel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ezekiel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ezekiel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:41:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/ezekiel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 37:21-28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ezekiel37_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:41:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ezekiel37_21-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And thou shalt say to them: Thus saith the Lord God: Behold, I will take of the children of Israel from the midst of the nations whither they are gone: and I will gather them on every side, and will bring them to their own land.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make them one nation in the land on the mountains of Israel, and one king shall be king over them all: and they shall no more be two nations, neither shall they be divided any more into two kingdoms.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Nor shall they be defiled any more with their idols, nor with their abominations, nor with all their iniquities: and I will save them out of all the places in which they have sinned, and I will cleanse them: and they shall be my people, and I will be their God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And my servant David shall be king over them, and they shall have one shepherd: they shall walk in my judgments, and shall keep my commandments, and shall do them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; And they shall dwell in the land which I gave to my servant Jacob, wherein your fathers dwelt, and they shall dwell in it, they and their children, and their children&amp;rsquo;s children, for ever: and David my servant shall be their prince for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And I will make a covenant of peace with them, it shall be an everlasting covenant with them: and I will establish them, and will multiply them, and will set my sanctuary in the midst of them for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And my tabernacle shall be with them: and I will be their God, and they shall be my people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And the nations shall know that I am the Lord the sanctifier of Israel, when my sanctuary shall be in the midst of them for ever .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die? saith the Lord GOD: and not that he should return from his ways, and live?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But when the righteous turneth away from his righteousness, and committeth iniquity, and doeth according to all the abominations that the wicked man doeth, shall he live? All his righteousness that he hath done shall not be mentioned: in his trespass that he hath trespassed, and in his sin that he hath sinned, in them shall he die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Yet ye say, The way of the Lord is not equal. Hear now, O house of Israel; Is not my way equal? are not your ways unequal?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; When a righteous man turneth away from his righteousness, and committeth iniquity, and dieth in them; for his iniquity that he hath done shall he die.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Again, when the wicked man turneth away from his wickedness that he hath committed, and doeth that which is lawful and right, he shall save his soul alive.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Because he considereth, and turneth away from all his transgressions that he hath committed, he shall surely live, he shall not die.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
