<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/nt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/nt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Palm Sunday</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/palm-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/palm-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Mark 14 14:1 Now the feast of the Passover and of the unleavened bread was after two days: and the chief priests and the scribes sought how they might by some wile lay hold on him, and kill him. 2 But they said: Not on the festival day, lest there should be a tumult among the people. 3 And when he was in Bethania, in the house of Simon the leper, and was at meat, there came a woman, having an alabaster box of ointment of precious spikenard: and breaking the alabaster box, she poured it out upon his head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 11:45-56</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john11_45-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:45:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john11_45-56/</guid>
      <description>Reading 45 Many therefore of the Jews, who were come to Mary and Martha and had seen the things that Jesus did, believed in him.
46 But some of them went to the Pharisees and told them the things that Jesus had done.
47 The chief priests, therefore, and the Pharisees gathered a council and said: What do we, for this man doth many miracles?
48 If we let him alone so, all will believe in him; and the Romans will come, and take away our place and nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 10:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john10_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john10_31-42/</guid>
      <description>Reading 31 The Jews then took up stones to stone him.
32 Jesus answered them: Many good works I have shewed you from my Father. For which of those works do you stone me?
33 The Jews answered him: For a good work we stone thee not, but for blasphemy: and because that thou, being a man, makest thyself God.
34 Jesus answered them: Is it not written in your law: I said, you are gods?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:51-59</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_51-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_51-59/</guid>
      <description>Reading 51 Amen, amen, I say to you: If any man keep my word, he shall not see death for ever.
52 The Jews therefore said: Now we know that thou hast a devil. Abraham is dead, and the prophets: and thou sayest: If any man keep my word, he shall not taste death for ever.
53 Art thou greater than our father Abraham who is dead? And the prophets are dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:05:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_31-42/</guid>
      <description>Reading 31 Then Jesus said to those Jews, who believed him: If you continue in my word, you shall be my disciples indeed.
32 And you shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.
33 They answered him: We are the seed of Abraham, and we have never been slaves to any man: how sayest thou: You shall be free?
34 Jesus answered them: Amen, amen I say unto you: that whosoever committeth sin, is the servant of sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 1:16-24</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew1_16-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 03:26:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew1_16-24/</guid>
      <description>Reading 16 And Jacob begot Joseph the husband of Mary, of whom was born Jesus, who is called Christ.
18 Now the birth of Jesus Christ was on this wise: When as his mother Mary was espoused to Joseph, before they came together, she was found with child of the Holy Ghost.
19 Then Joseph her husband, being a just man, and not willing to make her a public example, was minded to put her away privily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 8:1-11</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_1-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:09:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john8_1-11/</guid>
      <description>Reading 1 And Jesus went unto mount Olivet.
2 And early in the morning he came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and sitting down, he taught them.
3 And the scribes and the Pharisees bring unto him a woman taken in adultery; and when they had set her in the midst,
4 They say unto him: Master, this woman was taken in adultery, in the very act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 7:40-53</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john740-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john740-53/</guid>
      <description>Reading 40 Of that multitude therefore, when they had heard these words of his, some said: This is the prophet indeed. 41 Others said: This is the Christ. But some said: Doth the Christ come out of Galilee? 42 Doth not the scripture say: That Christ cometh of the seed of David, and from Bethlehem the town where David was? 43 So there arose a dissension among the people because of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 7:2,10,25-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:01:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</guid>
      <description>Reading 1 After these things Jesus walked in Galilee; for he would not walk in Judea, because the Jews sought to kill him. 2 Now the Jews&#39; feast of tabernacles was at hand. 10 But when his brethren were gone up, then went he also up unto the feast, not openly, but as it were in secret. 25 Then said some of them of Jerusalem, Is not this he, whom they seek to kill?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 15:12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john15_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:46:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john15_12-17/</guid>
      <description>Reading 12 This is my commandment, That you love one another, as I have loved you. 13 Greater love than this no man hath, that a man lay down his life for his friends. 14 You are my friends, if you do the things that I command you. 15 I will not now call you servants: for the servant knoweth not what his lord doth. But I have called you friends: because all things whatsoever I have heard of my Father, I have made known to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 5:17-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john5_17-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john5_17-30/</guid>
      <description>Reading 17 But Jesus answered them, &amp;ldquo;My Father is at work until now, so I am at work.&amp;rdquo; 18 For this reason the Jews tried all the more to kill him, because he not only broke the sabbath but he also called God his own father, making himself equal to God. 19 Jesus answered and said to them, &amp;ldquo;Amen, amen, I say to you, the Son cannot do anything on his own, but only what he sees the Father doing; for what he does, the Son will do also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 4:43-54</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john4_43-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john4_43-54/</guid>
      <description>Reading 43. At that time Jesus left [Samaria] for Galilee. 44. For Jesus himself testified that a prophet has no honor in his native place. 45. When he came into Galilee, the Galileans welcomed him, since they had seen all he had done in Jerusalem at the feast; for they themselves had gone to the feast. &amp;hellip; 54. Now this was the second sign Jesus did when he came to Galilee from Judea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 25:31-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew25_31-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:55:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew25_31-46/</guid>
      <description>Matthew 25:31-46
31. &amp;ldquo;When the Son of man shall come in his majesty, and all the angels with him, then shall he sit upon the seat of his majesty.
32. And all nations shall be gathered together before him: and he shall separate them one from another, as the shepherd separateth the sheep from the goats:
33. And he shall set the sheep on his right hand, but the goats on his left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 18:9-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke18_9-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke18_9-14/</guid>
      <description>9 And he spake this parable unto certain which trusted in themselves that they were righteous, and despised others:
10 Two men went up into the temple to pray; the one a Pharisee, and the other a publican.
11 The Pharisee stood and prayed thus with himself, God, I thank thee, that I am not as other men are, extortioners, unjust, adulterers, or even as this publican.
12 I fast twice in the week, I give tithes of all that I possess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acts 1:12-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/acts112-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/acts112-14/</guid>
      <description>Feast Day The Memorial of The Blessed Virgin Mary, Mother of the Church, which is observed during the Tenth Week in Ordinary Time
Reading Acts 1:12-14 12. Then they returned to Jerusalem from the mount that is called Olivet, which is nigh Jerusalem, within a sabbath day&amp;rsquo;s journey.
13. And when they were come in, they went up into an upper room, where abode Peter and John, James and Andrew, Philip and Thomas, Bartholomew and Matthew, James of Alpheus and Simon Zelotes and Jude the brother of James.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark 12:28-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/mark12_28-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:16:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/mark12_28-34/</guid>
      <description>28 And one of the scribes came, and having heard them reasoning together, and perceiving that he had answered them well, asked him, Which is the first commandment of all?
29 And Jesus answered him, The first of all the commandments is, Hear, O Israel; The Lord our God is one Lord:
30 And thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy mind, and with all thy strength: this is the first commandment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 11:14-23</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke11_14-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke11_14-23/</guid>
      <description>Luke 11:14-23 14 And he was casting out a devil, and it was dumb. And it came to pass, when the devil was gone out, the dumb spake; and the people wondered. 15 But some of them said, He casteth out devils through Beelzebub the chief of the devils. 16 And others, tempting him, sought of him a sign from heaven. 17 But he, knowing their thoughts, said unto them, Every kingdom divided against itself is brought to desolation; and a house divided against a house falleth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:17-19</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_17-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:17:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_17-19/</guid>
      <description>17 Think not that I am come to destroy the law, or the prophets: I am not come to destroy, but to fulfil.
18 For verily I say unto you, Till heaven and earth pass, one jot or one tittle shall in no wise pass from the law, till all be fulfilled.
19 Whosoever therefore shall break one of these least commandments, and shall teach men so, he shall be called the least in the kingdom of heaven: but whosoever shall do and teach them, the same shall be called great in the kingdom of heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 18:21-35</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew18_21-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:17:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew18_21-35/</guid>
      <description>21 Then came Peter to him, and said, Lord, how oft shall my brother sin against me, and I forgive him? till seven times?
22 Jesus saith unto him, I say not unto thee, Until seven times: but, Until seventy times seven.
23 Therefore is the kingdom of heaven likened unto a certain king, which would take account of his servants.
24 And when he had begun to reckon, one was brought unto him, which owed him ten thousand talents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 4:24-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke4_24-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:48:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke4_24-30/</guid>
      <description>24 And he said, Verily I say unto you, No prophet is accepted in his own country.
25 But I tell you of a truth, many widows were in Israel in the days of Elias, when the heaven was shut up three years and six months, when great famine was throughout all the land; 26 But unto none of them was Elias sent, save unto Sarepta, a city of Sidon, unto a woman that was a widow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>13 And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.
14 And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: 15 And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; 16 And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians 1:22-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:10:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</guid>
      <description>22 For the Jews require a sign, and the Greeks seek after wisdom: 23 But we preach Christ crucified, unto the Jews a stumblingblock, and unto the Greeks foolishness; 24 But unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks, Christ the power of God, and the wisdom of God. 25 Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men【34†source】.
ChatGPT Response Here is the image inspired by 1 Corinthians 1:22-25, capturing the contrast between human wisdom and divine wisdom, with a focus on the symbolic power of the cross as the unifying element of God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom over human understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 15:1-3, 11-32</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:24:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</guid>
      <description>1 Then drew near unto him all the publicans and sinners for to hear him.
2 And the Pharisees and scribes murmured, saying, This man receiveth sinners, and eateth with them.
3 And he spake this parable unto them, saying,
11 And he said, A certain man had two sons:
12 And the younger of them said to his father, Father, give me the portion of goods that falleth to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 21:33-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew21_33-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew21_33-46/</guid>
      <description>33 Hear another parable: There was a certain householder, which planted a vineyard, and hedged it round about, and digged a winepress in it, and built a tower, and let it out to husbandmen, and went into a far country: 34 And when the time of the fruit drew near, he sent his servants to the husbandmen, that they might receive the fruits of it. 35 And the husbandmen took his servants, and beat one, and killed another, and stoned another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke16_19 31</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke16_19-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:57:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke16_19-31/</guid>
      <description>19 There was a certain rich man, which was clothed in purple and fine linen, and fared sumptuously every day: 20 And there was a certain beggar named Lazarus, which was laid at his gate, full of sores, 21 And desiring to be fed with the crumbs which fell from the rich man&amp;rsquo;s table: moreover the dogs came and licked his sores. 22 And it came to pass, that the beggar died, and was carried by the angels into Abraham&amp;rsquo;s bosom: the rich man also died, and was buried; 23 And in hell he lift up his eyes, being in torments, and seeth Abraham afar off, and Lazarus in his bosom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 20:17-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew20_17-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew20_17-28/</guid>
      <description>17 And Jesus going up to Jerusalem took the twelve disciples apart in the way, and said unto them,
18 Behold, we go up to Jerusalem; and the Son of man shall be betrayed unto the chief priests and unto the scribes, and they shall condemn him to death,
19 And shall deliver him to the Gentiles to mock, and to scourge, and to crucify him: and the third day he shall rise again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23:1-12</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew23_1-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew23_1-12/</guid>
      <description>1 Then spake Jesus to the multitude, and to his disciples,
2 Saying, The scribes and the Pharisees sit in Moses&#39; seat:
3 All therefore whatsoever they bid you observe, that observe and do; but do not ye after their works: for they say, and do not.
4 For they bind heavy burdens and grievous to be borne, and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 6:36-38</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</guid>
      <description>36 Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful.
37 Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shall be forgiven:
38 Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark 9:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:56:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</guid>
      <description>2 And after six days Jesus taketh with him Peter, and James, and John, and leadeth them up into a high mountain apart by themselves: and he was transfigured before them.
3 And his raiment became shining, exceeding white as snow; so as no fuller on earth can white them.
4 And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.
5 And Peter answered and said to Jesus, Master, it is good for us to be here: and let us make three tabernacles; one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans 8:31-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/rom8_31-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/rom8_31-34/</guid>
      <description>31 What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?
32 He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?
33 Who shall lay any thing to the charge of God’s elect? It is God that justifieth.
34 Who is he that condemneth? It is Christ that died, yea rather, that is risen again, who is even at the right hand of God, who also maketh intercession for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>43 Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.
44 But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;
45 That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>20 For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.
21 Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: 22 But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
