<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deutronomy on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/deutronomy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deutronomy on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:16:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/deutronomy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 4:1,5-9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:16:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Now therefore hearken, O Israel, unto the statutes and unto the judgments, which I teach you, for to do them, that ye may live, and go in and possess the land which the LORD God of your fathers giveth you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Behold, I have taught you statutes and judgments, even as the LORD my God commanded me, that ye should do so in the land whither ye go to possess it.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; Keep therefore and do them; for this is your wisdom and your understanding in the sight of the nations, which shall hear all these statutes, and say, Surely this great nation is a wise and understanding people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; For what nation is there so great, who hath God so nigh unto them, as the LORD our God is in all things that we call upon him for?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And what nation is there so great, that hath statutes and judgments so righteous as all this law, which I set before you this day?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Only take heed to thyself, and keep thy soul diligently, lest thou forget the things which thine eyes have seen, and lest they depart from thy heart all the days of thy life: but teach them thy sons, and thy sons&amp;rsquo; sons;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
