<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosea on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.art/tags/hosea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hosea on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://matthew419.art/tags/hosea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 6:1-6</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea6_1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea6_1-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Come, and let us return unto the LORD: for he hath torn, and he will heal us; he hath smitten, and he will bind us up.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; After two days will he revive us: in the third day he will raise us up, and we shall live in his sight.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Then shall we know, if we follow on to know the LORD: his going forth is prepared as the morning; and he shall come unto us as the rain, as the latter and former rain unto the earth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; O Ephraim, what shall I do unto thee? O Judah, what shall I do unto thee? for your goodness is as a morning cloud, and as the early dew it goeth away.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore have I hewed them by the prophets; I have slain them by the words of my mouth: and thy judgments are as the light that goeth forth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; For I desired mercy, and not sacrifice; and the knowledge of God more than burnt offerings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 14:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea14_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:15:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/hosea14_2-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Take with you words, and turn to the LORD: say unto him, Take away all iniquity, and receive us graciously: so will we render the calves of our lips.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Asshur shall not save us; we will not ride upon horses: neither will we say any more to the work of our hands, Ye are our gods: for in thee the fatherless findeth mercy.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; I will heal their backsliding, I will love them freely: for mine anger is turned away from him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; I will be as the dew unto Israel: he shall grow as the lily, and cast forth his roots as Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; His branches shall spread, and his beauty shall be as the olive tree, and his smell as Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; They that dwell under his shadow shall return; they shall revive as the corn, and grow as the vine: the scent thereof shall be as the wine of Lebanon.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Ephraim shall say, What have I to do any more with idols? I have heard him, and observed him: I am like a green fir tree. From me is thy fruit found.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Who is wise, and he shall understand these things? prudent, and he shall know them? for the ways of the LORD are right, and the just shall walk in them: but the transgressors shall fall therein.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
