<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Palm Sunday</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/palm-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/palm-sunday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mark-14&#34;&gt;Mark 14&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14:1&lt;/strong&gt; Now the feast of the Passover and of the unleavened bread was after two days: and the chief priests and the scribes sought how they might by some wile lay hold on him, and kill him. &lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; But they said: Not on the festival day, lest there should be a tumult among the people. &lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And when he was in Bethania, in the house of Simon the leper, and was at meat, there came a woman, having an alabaster box of ointment of precious spikenard: and breaking the alabaster box, she poured it out upon his head. &lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; Now there were some that had indignation within themselves, and said: Why was this waste of the ointment made? &lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; For this ointment might have been sold for more than three hundred pence, and given to the poor. And they murmured against her. &lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus said: Let her alone, why do you molest her? She hath wrought a good work upon me. &lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; For the poor you have always with you: and whensoever you will, you may do them good: but me you have not always. &lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; She hath done what she could: she is come beforehand to anoint my body for the burial. &lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Amen I say to you, wheresoever this gospel shall be preached in the whole world, that also which she hath done, shall be told for a memory of her. &lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; And Judas Iscariot, one of the twelve, went to the chief priests, to betray him to them. &lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; Who hearing it were glad; and they promised him they would give him money. And he sought how he might conveniently betray him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy Thursday - Evening Mass of The Lord&#39;s Supper</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/holy-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:03:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/holy-thursday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;john-131-15-from-the-douay-rheims-bible&#34;&gt;John 13:1-15 from the Douay-Rheims Bible:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711238649/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_1_u4bshu.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Before the festival day of the pasch, Jesus knowing that his hour was come, that he should pass out of this world to the Father: having loved his own who were in the world, he loved them unto the end.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711238734/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_2_osy96s.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And when supper was done (the devil having now put into the heart of Judas Iscariot, the son of Simon, to betray him),&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239089/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_3_x7tisg.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; Knowing that the Father had given him all things into his hands and that he came from God and goeth to God,&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239185/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_4_kjycfb.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; He riseth from supper and layeth aside his garments and, having taken a towel, girded himself.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239320/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_5_msfkg1.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; After that, he putteth water into a basin and began to wash the feet of the disciples and to wipe them with the towel wherewith he was girded.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239416/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_6_puxdbk.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; He cometh therefore to Simon Peter. And Peter saith to him: Lord, dost thou wash my feet?&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239525/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_7_un26je.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered and said to him: What I do, thou knowest not now; but thou shalt know hereafter.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239627/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_8_mw3cg5.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; Peter saith to him: Thou shalt never wash my feet, Jesus answered him: If I wash thee not, thou shalt have no part with me.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239735/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_9_glbq6o.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Simon Peter saith to him: Lord, not only my feet, but also my hands and my head.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239836/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_10_umsc7m.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith to him: He that is washed needeth not but to wash his feet, but is clean wholly. And you are clean, but not all.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711239972/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_11_ws6pum.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; For he knew who he was that would betray him; therefore he said: You are not all clean.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711240090/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_12_yhk1pl.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; Then after he had washed their feet and taken his garments, being set down again, he said to them: Know you what I have done to you?&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711240182/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_13_gexovy.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; You call me Master and Lord. And you say well: for so I am.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711240351/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_14_dody4n.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; If then I being your Lord and Master, have washed your feet; you also ought to wash one another&amp;rsquo;s feet.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dafjqauwb/image/upload/v1711240455/matt419/HolyThursday/John13_15_sakwbt.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; For I have given you an example, that as I have done to you, so you do also .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasterSunday2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/eastersunday2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:04:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/eastersunday2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;feast-day&#34;&gt;Feast Day&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;chatgpt-response&#34;&gt;ChatGPT Response&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HolySaturday2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/holysaturday2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:04:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/holysaturday2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;feast-day&#34;&gt;Feast Day&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;chatgpt-response&#34;&gt;ChatGPT Response&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoodFriday2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/goodfriday2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/goodfriday2024/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stations of the Cross</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sotc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:38:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sotc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This proved to be more difficult to produce than I had originally considered. ChatGPT has content filters for what it can produce when asked. We (at least I) tend to think of the Bible in nursery rhymes or that it is G rated. However nothing could be further from the truth. Most Roman Catholics and Orthodox have an effigy of a man nailed to a cross, which has been normalized into our conciseness since our birth. The truth is that the Bible deals with very adult themes. From torture to what some might call genocide, and many things in between. Asking ChatGPT to make images that were inspired by some of the Stations of The Cross often failed as they were not acceptable to the content filters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:05:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Norm. Thank you for visiting!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The images used on this site are generated using OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT. The verses are from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dynamiccatholic.com&#34;&gt;dail Mass readings&lt;/a&gt; so we will make our journy through the Bible in 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All images on this site come from ChatGPT unless specified otherwise. They are also free for you to use, though attribution and a donation would be nice, it is not required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
