<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gospel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.art/tags/the-gospel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Gospel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://matthew419.art/tags/the-gospel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Palm Sunday</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/palm-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/palm-sunday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mark-14&#34;&gt;Mark 14&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14:1&lt;/strong&gt; Now the feast of the Passover and of the unleavened bread was after two days: and the chief priests and the scribes sought how they might by some wile lay hold on him, and kill him. &lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; But they said: Not on the festival day, lest there should be a tumult among the people. &lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And when he was in Bethania, in the house of Simon the leper, and was at meat, there came a woman, having an alabaster box of ointment of precious spikenard: and breaking the alabaster box, she poured it out upon his head. &lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; Now there were some that had indignation within themselves, and said: Why was this waste of the ointment made? &lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; For this ointment might have been sold for more than three hundred pence, and given to the poor. And they murmured against her. &lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus said: Let her alone, why do you molest her? She hath wrought a good work upon me. &lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; For the poor you have always with you: and whensoever you will, you may do them good: but me you have not always. &lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; She hath done what she could: she is come beforehand to anoint my body for the burial. &lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; Amen I say to you, wheresoever this gospel shall be preached in the whole world, that also which she hath done, shall be told for a memory of her. &lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; And Judas Iscariot, one of the twelve, went to the chief priests, to betray him to them. &lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; Who hearing it were glad; and they promised him they would give him money. And he sought how he might conveniently betray him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 11:45-56</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john11_45-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:45:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john11_45-56/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; Many therefore of the Jews, who were come to Mary and Martha and had seen the things that Jesus did, believed in him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;46&lt;/strong&gt; But some of them went to the Pharisees and told them the things that Jesus had done.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;47&lt;/strong&gt; The chief priests, therefore, and the Pharisees gathered a council and said: What do we, for this man doth many miracles?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;48&lt;/strong&gt; If we let him alone so, all will believe in him; and the Romans will come, and take away our place and nation.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;49&lt;/strong&gt; But one of them, named Caiphas, being the high priest that year, said to them: You know nothing.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;50&lt;/strong&gt; Neither do you consider that it is expedient for you that one man should die for the people and that the whole nation perish not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; And this he spoke not of himself: but being the high priest of that year, he prophesied that Jesus should die for the nation.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; And not only for the nation, but to gather together in one the children of God that were dispersed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; From that day therefore they devised to put him to death.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54&lt;/strong&gt; Wherefore Jesus walked no more openly among the Jews: but he went into a country near the desert, unto a city that is called Ephrem. And there he abode with his disciples.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;55&lt;/strong&gt; And the pasch of the Jews was at hand: and many from the country went up to Jerusalem, before the pasch, to purify themselves.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;56&lt;/strong&gt; They sought therefore for Jesus; and they discoursed one with another, standing in the temple: What think you that he is not come to the festival day? And the chief priests and Pharisees had given a commandment that, if any man knew where he was, he should tell, that they might apprehend him .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 10:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john10_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john10_31-42/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews then took up stones to stone him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Many good works I have shewed you from my Father. For which of those works do you stone me?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews answered him: For a good work we stone thee not, but for blasphemy: and because that thou, being a man, makest thyself God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Is it not written in your law: I said, you are gods?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; If he called them gods to whom the word of God was spoken; and the scripture cannot be broken:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Do you say of him whom the Father hath sanctified and sent into the world: Thou blasphemest; because I said: I am the Son of God?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; If I do not the works of my Father, believe me not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; But if I do, though you will not believe me, believe the works: that you may know and believe that the Father is in me and I in the Father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; They sought therefore to take him: and he escaped out of their hands.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; And he went again beyond the Jordan, into that place where John was baptizing first. And there he abode.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; And many resorted to him: and they said: John indeed did no sign.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; But all things whatsoever John said of this man were true. And many believed in him .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:51-59</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_51-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_51-59/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you: If any man keep my word, he shall not see death for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews therefore said: Now we know that thou hast a devil. Abraham is dead, and the prophets: and thou sayest: If any man keep my word, he shall not taste death for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; Art thou greater than our father Abraham who is dead? And the prophets are dead. Whom dost thou make thyself?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered: If I glorify myself, my glory is nothing. It is my Father that glorifieth me, of whom you say that he is your God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;55&lt;/strong&gt; And you have not known him: but I know him. And if I shall say that I know him not, I shall be like to you, a liar. But I do know him and do keep his word.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;56&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham your father rejoiced that he might see my day: he saw it and was glad.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;57&lt;/strong&gt; The Jews therefore said to him: Thou art not yet fifty years old. And hast thou seen Abraham?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;58&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus said to them: Amen, amen, I say to you, before Abraham was made, I AM.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;59&lt;/strong&gt; They took up stones therefore to cast at him. But Jesus hid himself and went out of the temple .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:31-42</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_31-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:05:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_31-42/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; Then Jesus said to those Jews, who believed him: If you continue in my word, you shall be my disciples indeed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; And you shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; They answered him: We are the seed of Abraham, and we have never been slaves to any man: how sayest thou: You shall be free?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered them: Amen, amen I say unto you: that whosoever committeth sin, is the servant of sin.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And the servant abideth not in the house for ever; but the Son abideth for ever.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; If therefore the Son shall make you free, you shall be free indeed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; I know that you are the children of Abraham: but you seek to kill me, because my word hath no place in you.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; I speak that which I have seen with my Father: and you do the things that you have seen with your father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; They answered, and said to him: Abraham is our father. Jesus saith to them: If you be the children of Abraham, do the works of Abraham.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; But now you seek to kill me, a man who have spoken to you the truth, which I have heard of God. This Abraham did not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; You do the works of your father. They said therefore to him: We are not born of fornication; we have one Father, even God.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus said to them: If God were your Father, you would indeed love me. For from God I proceeded, and came; for I came not of myself, but he sent me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 1:16-24</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew1_16-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 03:26:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew1_16-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And Jacob begot Joseph the husband of Mary, of whom was born Jesus, who is called Christ.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Now the birth of Jesus Christ was on this wise: When as his mother Mary was espoused to Joseph, before they came together, she was found with child of the Holy Ghost.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Then Joseph her husband, being a just man, and not willing to make her a public example, was minded to put her away privily.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But while he thought on these things, behold, the angel of the Lord appeared unto him in a dream, saying, Joseph, thou son of David, fear not to take unto thee Mary thy wife: for that which is conceived in her is of the Holy Ghost.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And she shall bring forth a son, and thou shalt call his name JESUS: for he shall save his people from their sins.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24a&lt;/strong&gt; Then Joseph being raised from sleep did as the angel of the Lord had bidden him, and took unto him his wife:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 8:1-11</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_1-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:09:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john8_1-11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus went unto mount Olivet.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And early in the morning he came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and sitting down, he taught them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And the scribes and the Pharisees bring unto him a woman taken in adultery; and when they had set her in the midst,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; They say unto him: Master, this woman was taken in adultery, in the very act.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Now Moses in the law commanded us, that such should be stoned. But what sayest thou?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; This they said, tempting him, that they might have to accuse him. But Jesus stooped down, and with his finger wrote on the ground, as though he heard them not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; So when they continued asking him, he lifted up himself, and said unto them: He that is without sin among you, let him first cast a stone at her.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; And again he stooped down, and wrote on the ground.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And they which heard it, being convicted by their own conscience, went out one by one, beginning at the eldest, even unto the last: and Jesus was left alone, and the woman standing in the midst.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; When Jesus had lifted up himself, and saw none but the woman, he said unto her: Woman, where are those thine accusers? hath no man condemned thee?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; She said, No man, Lord. And Jesus said unto her: Neither do I condemn thee: go, and sin no more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 7:40-53</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john740-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john740-53/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; Of that multitude therefore, when they had heard these words of his, some said: This is the prophet indeed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; Others said: This is the Christ. But some said: Doth the Christ come out of Galilee?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Doth not the scripture say: That Christ cometh of the seed of David, and from Bethlehem the town where David was?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; So there arose a dissension among the people because of him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;44&lt;/strong&gt; And some of them would have apprehended him: but no man laid hands upon him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; The ministers therefore came to the chief priests and the Pharisees. And they said to them: Why have you not brought him?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;46&lt;/strong&gt; The ministers answered: Never did man speak like this man.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;47&lt;/strong&gt; The Pharisees therefore answered them: Are you also seduced?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;48&lt;/strong&gt; Hath any one of the rulers believed in him, or of the Pharisees?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;49&lt;/strong&gt; But this multitude, that knoweth not the law, are accursed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;50&lt;/strong&gt; Nicodemus, he that came to him by night, who was one of them, saith to them:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;51&lt;/strong&gt; Doth our law judge any man, unless it first hear him, and know what he doth?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt; They answered, and said to him: Art thou also a Galilean? Search the scriptures, and see that out of Galilee a prophet riseth not.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;53&lt;/strong&gt; And every man returned to his own house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 7:2,10,25-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 02:01:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john7_2_10_25-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; After these things Jesus walked in Galilee; for he would not walk in Judea, because the Jews sought to kill him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Now the Jews&amp;rsquo; feast of tabernacles was at hand.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; But when his brethren were gone up, then went he also up unto the feast, not openly, but as it were in secret.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Then said some of them of Jerusalem, Is not this he, whom they seek to kill?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And, lo, he speaketh boldly, and they say nothing unto him. Do the rulers know indeed that this is the very Christ?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Howbeit we know this man whence he is: but when Christ cometh, no man knoweth whence he is.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Then cried Jesus in the temple as he taught, saying, Ye both know me, and ye know whence I am: and I am not come of myself, but he that sent me is true, whom ye know not.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; But I know him: for I am from him, and he hath sent me.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; Then they sought to take him: but no man laid hands on him, because his hour was not yet come.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 15:12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john15_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:46:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john15_12-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; This is my commandment, That you love one another, as I have loved you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Greater love than this no man hath, that a man lay down his life for his friends.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; You are my friends, if you do the things that I command you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; I will not now call you servants: for the servant knoweth not what his lord doth. But I have called you friends: because all things whatsoever I have heard of my Father, I have made known to you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; You have not chosen me: but I have chosen you; and have appointed you, that you should go, and should bring forth fruit; and your fruit should remain: that whatsoever you shall ask of the Father in my name, he may give it you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; These things I command you, that you love one another.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 5:17-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john5_17-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john5_17-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus answered them, &amp;ldquo;My Father is at work until now, so I am at work.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; For this reason the Jews tried all the more to kill him, because he not only broke the sabbath but he also called God his own father, making himself equal to God.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus answered and said to them, &amp;ldquo;Amen, amen, I say to you, the Son cannot do anything on his own, but only what he sees the Father doing; for what he does, the Son will do also.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; For the Father loves the Son and shows him everything that he himself does, and he will show him greater works than these, so that you may be amazed.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; For just as the Father raises the dead and gives life, so also does the Son give life to whomever he wishes.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; Nor does the Father judge anyone, but he has given all judgment to the Son,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; so that all may honor the Son just as they honor the Father. Whoever does not honor the Son does not honor the Father who sent him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you, whoever hears my word and believes in the one who sent me has eternal life and will not come to condemnation, but has passed from death to life.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Amen, amen, I say to you, the hour is coming and is now here when the dead will hear the voice of the Son of God, and those who hear will live.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; For just as the Father has life in himself, so also he gave to his Son the possession of life in himself.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And he gave him power to exercise judgment, because he is the Son of Man.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Do not be amazed at this, because the hour is coming in which all who are in the tombs will hear his voice&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; and will come out, those who have done good deeds to the resurrection of life, but those who have done wicked deeds to the resurrection of condemnation.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I cannot do anything on my own; I judge as I hear, and my judgment is just, because I do not seek my own will but the will of the one who sent me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 4:43-54</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john4_43-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john4_43-54/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;43.&lt;/strong&gt; At that time Jesus left [Samaria] for Galilee.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;44.&lt;/strong&gt; For Jesus himself testified that a prophet has no honor in his native place.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;45.&lt;/strong&gt; When he came into Galilee, the Galileans welcomed him, since they had seen all he had done in Jerusalem at the feast; for they themselves had gone to the feast.&#xA;&amp;hellip;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;54.&lt;/strong&gt; Now this was the second sign Jesus did when he came to Galilee from Judea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 25:31-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew25_31-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:55:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew25_31-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matthew 25:31-46&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;When the Son of man shall come in his majesty, and all the angels with him, then shall he sit upon the seat of his majesty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32.&lt;/strong&gt; And all nations shall be gathered together before him: and he shall separate them one from another, as the shepherd separateth the sheep from the goats:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33.&lt;/strong&gt; And he shall set the sheep on his right hand, but the goats on his left.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 18:9-14</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke18_9-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke18_9-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And he spake this parable unto certain which trusted in themselves that they were righteous, and despised others:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Two men went up into the temple to pray; the one a Pharisee, and the other a publican.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; The Pharisee stood and prayed thus with himself, God, I thank thee, that I am not as other men are, extortioners, unjust, adulterers, or even as this publican.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; I fast twice in the week, I give tithes of all that I possess.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And the publican, standing afar off, would not lift up so much as his eyes unto heaven, but smote upon his breast, saying, God be merciful to me a sinner.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; I tell you, this man went down to his house justified rather than the other: for every one that exalteth himself shall be abased.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark 12:28-34</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/mark12_28-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:16:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/mark12_28-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And one of the scribes came, and having heard them reasoning together, and perceiving that he had answered them well, asked him, Which is the first commandment of all?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus answered him, The first of all the commandments is, Hear, O Israel; The Lord our God is one Lord:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; And thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy mind, and with all thy strength: this is the first commandment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 11:14-23</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke11_14-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke11_14-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;luke-1114-23&#34;&gt;Luke 11:14-23&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And he was casting out a devil, and it was dumb. And it came to pass, when the devil was gone out, the dumb spake; and the people wondered.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; But some of them said, He casteth out devils through Beelzebub the chief of the devils.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And others, tempting him, sought of him a sign from heaven.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; But he, knowing their thoughts, said unto them, Every kingdom divided against itself is brought to desolation; and a house divided against a house falleth.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; If Satan also be divided against himself, how shall his kingdom stand? because ye say that I cast out devils through Beelzebub.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And if I by Beelzebub cast out devils, by whom do your sons cast them out? therefore shall they be your judges.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But if I with the finger of God cast out devils, no doubt the kingdom of God is come upon you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; When a strong man armed keepeth his palace, his goods are in peace:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But when a stronger than he shall come upon him, and overcome him, he taketh from him all his armour wherein he trusted, and divideth his spoils.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; He that is not with me is against me: and he that gathereth not with me scattereth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:17-19</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_17-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:17:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_17-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Think not that I am come to destroy the law, or the prophets: I am not come to destroy, but to fulfil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; For verily I say unto you, Till heaven and earth pass, one jot or one tittle shall in no wise pass from the law, till all be fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Whosoever therefore shall break one of these least commandments, and shall teach men so, he shall be called the least in the kingdom of heaven: but whosoever shall do and teach them, the same shall be called great in the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 18:21-35</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew18_21-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:17:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew18_21-35/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; Then came Peter to him, and said, Lord, how oft shall my brother sin against me, and I forgive him? till seven times?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith unto him, I say not unto thee, Until seven times: but, Until seventy times seven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore is the kingdom of heaven likened unto a certain king, which would take account of his servants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had begun to reckon, one was brought unto him, which owed him ten thousand talents.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 4:24-30</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke4_24-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:48:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke4_24-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Verily I say unto you, No prophet is accepted in his own country.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But I tell you of a truth, many widows were in Israel in the days of Elias, when the heaven was shut up three years and six months, when great famine was throughout all the land; &lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; But unto none of them was Elias sent, save unto Sarepta, a city of Sidon, unto a woman that was a widow.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And many lepers were in Israel in the time of Eliseus the prophet; and none of them was cleansed, saving Naaman the Syrian.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And all they in the synagogue, when they heard these things, were filled with wrath, &lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And rose up, and thrust him out of the city, and led him unto the brow of the hill whereon their city was built, that they might cast him down headlong.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; But he passing through the midst of them went his way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: &lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; &lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians 1:22-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:10:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; For the Jews require a sign, and the Greeks seek after wisdom:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; But we preach Christ crucified, unto the Jews a stumblingblock, and unto the Greeks foolishness;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks, Christ the power of God, and the wisdom of God.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men【34†source】.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;chatgpt-response&#34;&gt;ChatGPT Response&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the image inspired by 1 Corinthians 1:22-25, capturing the contrast between human wisdom and divine wisdom, with a focus on the symbolic power of the cross as the unifying element of God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom over human understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 15:1-3, 11-32</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:24:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Then drew near unto him all the publicans and sinners for to hear him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And the Pharisees and scribes murmured, saying, This man receiveth sinners, and eateth with them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And he spake this parable unto them, saying,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, A certain man had two sons:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And the younger of them said to his father, Father, give me the portion of goods that falleth to me. And he divided unto them his living.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; And not many days after the younger son gathered all together, and took his journey into a far country, and there wasted his substance with riotous living.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt; And when he had spent all, there arose a mighty famine in that land; and he began to be in want.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; And he went and joined himself to a citizen of that country; and he sent him into his fields to feed swine.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;16&lt;/strong&gt; And he would fain have filled his belly with the husks that the swine did eat: and no man gave unto him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; And when he came to himself, he said, How many hired servants of my father’s have bread enough and to spare, and I perish with hunger!&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; I will arise and go to my father, and will say unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and before thee,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And am no more worthy to be called thy son: make me as one of thy hired servants.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; And he arose, and came to his father. But when he was yet a great way off, his father saw him, and had compassion, and ran, and fell on his neck, and kissed him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And the son said unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and in thy sight, and am no more worthy to be called thy son.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But the father said to his servants, Bring forth the best robe, and put it on him; and put a ring on his hand, and shoes on his feet:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And bring hither the fatted calf, and kill it; and let us eat, and be merry:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; For this my son was dead, and is alive again; he was lost, and is found. And they began to be merry.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Now his elder son was in the field: and as he came and drew nigh to the house, he heard musick and dancing.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And he called one of the servants, and asked what these things meant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, Thy brother is come; and thy father hath killed the fatted calf, because he hath received him safe and sound.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; And he was angry, and would not go in: therefore came his father out, and intreated him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; And he answering said to his father, Lo, these many years do I serve thee, neither transgressed I at any time thy commandment: and yet thou never gavest me a kid, that I might make merry with my friends:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; But as soon as this thy son was come, which hath devoured thy living with harlots, thou hast killed for him the fatted calf.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, Son, thou art ever with me, and all that I have is thine.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;32&lt;/strong&gt; It was meet that we should make merry, and be glad: for this thy brother was dead, and is alive again; and was lost, and is found.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 21:33-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew21_33-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew21_33-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; Hear another parable: There was a certain householder, which planted a vineyard, and hedged it round about, and digged a winepress in it, and built a tower, and let it out to husbandmen, and went into a far country:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; And when the time of the fruit drew near, he sent his servants to the husbandmen, that they might receive the fruits of it.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And the husbandmen took his servants, and beat one, and killed another, and stoned another.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Again, he sent other servants more than the first: and they did unto them likewise.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; But last of all he sent unto them his son, saying, They will reverence my son.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; But when the husbandmen saw the son, they said among themselves, This is the heir; come, let us kill him, and let us seize on his inheritance.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; And they caught him, and cast him out of the vineyard, and slew him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; When the lord therefore of the vineyard cometh, what will he do unto those husbandmen?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; They say unto him, He will miserably destroy those wicked men, and will let out his vineyard unto other husbandmen, which shall render him the fruits in their seasons.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith unto them, Did ye never read in the scriptures, The stone which the builders rejected, the same is become the head of the corner: this is the Lord’s doing, and it is marvellous in our eyes?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore say I unto you, The kingdom of God shall be taken from you, and given to a nation bringing forth the fruits thereof.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke16_19 31</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke16_19-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:57:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke16_19-31/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; There was a certain rich man, which was clothed in purple and fine linen, and fared sumptuously every day:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; And there was a certain beggar named Lazarus, which was laid at his gate, full of sores,&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And desiring to be fed with the crumbs which fell from the rich man&amp;rsquo;s table: moreover the dogs came and licked his sores.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; And it came to pass, that the beggar died, and was carried by the angels into Abraham&amp;rsquo;s bosom: the rich man also died, and was buried;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And in hell he lift up his eyes, being in torments, and seeth Abraham afar off, and Lazarus in his bosom.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And he cried and said, Father Abraham, have mercy on me, and send Lazarus, that he may dip the tip of his finger in water, and cool my tongue; for I am tormented in this flame.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But Abraham said, Son, remember that thou in thy lifetime receivedst thy good things, and likewise Lazarus evil things: but now he is comforted, and thou art tormented.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; And beside all this, between us and you there is a great gulf fixed: so that they which would pass from hence to you cannot; neither can they pass to us, that would come from thence.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Then he said, I pray thee therefore, father, that thou wouldest send him to my father&amp;rsquo;s house:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; For I have five brethren; that he may testify unto them, lest they also come into this place of torment.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt; Abraham saith unto him, They have Moses and the prophets; let them hear them.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; And he said, Nay, father Abraham: but if one went unto them from the dead, they will repent.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;31&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto him, If they hear not Moses and the prophets, neither will they be persuaded, though one rose from the dead.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 20:17-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew20_17-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew20_17-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus going up to Jerusalem took the twelve disciples apart in the way, and said unto them,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Behold, we go up to Jerusalem; and the Son of man shall be betrayed unto the chief priests and unto the scribes, and they shall condemn him to death,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And shall deliver him to the Gentiles to mock, and to scourge, and to crucify him: and the third day he shall rise again.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; Then came to him the mother of Zebedee&amp;rsquo;s children with her sons, worshipping him, and desiring a certain thing of him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto her, What wilt thou? She saith unto him, Grant that these my two sons may sit, the one on thy right hand, and the other on the left, in thy kingdom.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus answered and said, Ye know not what ye ask. Are ye able to drink of the cup that I shall drink of, and to be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with? They say unto him, We are able.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And he saith unto them, Ye shall drink indeed of my cup, and be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with: but to sit on my right hand, and on my left, is not mine to give, but it shall be given to them for whom it is prepared of my Father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And when the ten heard it, they were moved with indignation against the two brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus called them unto him, and said, Ye know that the princes of the Gentiles exercise dominion over them, and they that are great exercise authority upon them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; But it shall not be so among you: but whosoever will be great among you, let him be your minister;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever will be chief among you, let him be your servant:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Even as the Son of man came not to be ministered unto, but to minister, and to give his life a ransom for many.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23:1-12</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew23_1-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew23_1-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Then spake Jesus to the multitude, and to his disciples,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Saying, The scribes and the Pharisees sit in Moses&amp;rsquo; seat:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; All therefore whatsoever they bid you observe, that observe and do; but do not ye after their works: for they say, and do not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; For they bind heavy burdens and grievous to be borne, and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; But all their works they do for to be seen of men: they make broad their phylacteries, and enlarge the borders of their garments,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; And love the uppermost rooms at feasts, and the chief seats in the synagogues,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And greetings in the markets, and to be called of men, Rabbi, Rabbi.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; But be not ye called Rabbi: for one is your Master, even Christ; and all ye are brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And call no man your father upon the earth: for one is your Father, which is in heaven.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Neither be ye called masters: for one is your Master, even Christ.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But he that is greatest among you shall be your servant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever shall exalt himself shall be abased; and he that shall humble himself shall be exalted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke 6:36-38</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/luke6_36-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/luke6_36-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shall be forgiven:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark 9:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/mark9_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:56:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/mark9_2-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; And after six days Jesus taketh with him Peter, and James, and John, and leadeth them up into a high mountain apart by themselves: and he was transfigured before them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; And his raiment became shining, exceeding white as snow; so as no fuller on earth can white them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; And Peter answered and said to Jesus, Master, it is good for us to be here: and let us make three tabernacles; one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;44&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: &lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
