<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gospel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/the-gospel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Gospel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/the-gospel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>John 2:13-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:20:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/john2_13-25/</guid>
      <description>13 And the Jews’ passover was at hand, and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.
14 And found in the temple those that sold oxen and sheep and doves, and the changers of money sitting: 15 And when he had made a scourge of small cords, he drove them all out of the temple, and the sheep, and the oxen; and poured out the changers’ money, and overthrew the tables; 16 And said unto them that sold doves, Take these things hence; make not my Father’s house an house of merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians 1:22-25</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:10:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/1corinthians1_22-25/</guid>
      <description>22 For the Jews require a sign, and the Greeks seek after wisdom: 23 But we preach Christ crucified, unto the Jews a stumblingblock, and unto the Greeks foolishness; 24 But unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks, Christ the power of God, and the wisdom of God. 25 Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men【34†source】.
ChatGPT Response Here is the image inspired by 1 Corinthians 1:22-25, capturing the contrast between human wisdom and divine wisdom, with a focus on the symbolic power of the cross as the unifying element of God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom over human understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 15:1-3, 11-32</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:24:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke15_1-3_11-32/</guid>
      <description>1 Then drew near unto him all the publicans and sinners for to hear him.
2 And the Pharisees and scribes murmured, saying, This man receiveth sinners, and eateth with them.
3 And he spake this parable unto them, saying,
11 And he said, A certain man had two sons:
12 And the younger of them said to his father, Father, give me the portion of goods that falleth to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 21:33-46</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew21_33-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew21_33-46/</guid>
      <description>33 Hear another parable: There was a certain householder, which planted a vineyard, and hedged it round about, and digged a winepress in it, and built a tower, and let it out to husbandmen, and went into a far country: 34 And when the time of the fruit drew near, he sent his servants to the husbandmen, that they might receive the fruits of it. 35 And the husbandmen took his servants, and beat one, and killed another, and stoned another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke16_19 31</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke16_19-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:57:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke16_19-31/</guid>
      <description>19 There was a certain rich man, which was clothed in purple and fine linen, and fared sumptuously every day: 20 And there was a certain beggar named Lazarus, which was laid at his gate, full of sores, 21 And desiring to be fed with the crumbs which fell from the rich man&amp;rsquo;s table: moreover the dogs came and licked his sores. 22 And it came to pass, that the beggar died, and was carried by the angels into Abraham&amp;rsquo;s bosom: the rich man also died, and was buried; 23 And in hell he lift up his eyes, being in torments, and seeth Abraham afar off, and Lazarus in his bosom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 20:17-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew20_17-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew20_17-28/</guid>
      <description>17 And Jesus going up to Jerusalem took the twelve disciples apart in the way, and said unto them,
18 Behold, we go up to Jerusalem; and the Son of man shall be betrayed unto the chief priests and unto the scribes, and they shall condemn him to death,
19 And shall deliver him to the Gentiles to mock, and to scourge, and to crucify him: and the third day he shall rise again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23:1-12</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew23_1-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew23_1-12/</guid>
      <description>1 Then spake Jesus to the multitude, and to his disciples,
2 Saying, The scribes and the Pharisees sit in Moses&#39; seat:
3 All therefore whatsoever they bid you observe, that observe and do; but do not ye after their works: for they say, and do not.
4 For they bind heavy burdens and grievous to be borne, and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke 6:36-38</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/luke6_36-38/</guid>
      <description>36 Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful.
37 Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shall be forgiven:
38 Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark 9:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:56:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/mark9_2-10/</guid>
      <description>2 And after six days Jesus taketh with him Peter, and James, and John, and leadeth them up into a high mountain apart by themselves: and he was transfigured before them.
3 And his raiment became shining, exceeding white as snow; so as no fuller on earth can white them.
4 And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.
5 And Peter answered and said to Jesus, Master, it is good for us to be here: and let us make three tabernacles; one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>43 Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.
44 But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;
45 That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>20 For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.
21 Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: 22 But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
