<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/ot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:54:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/ot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus 19:1 2, 11-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/leviticus19_1-2_11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:54:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/leviticus19_1-2_11-18/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus 19:1-2, 11-18
The Lord spoke to Moses, saying:
2. &amp;ldquo;Speak to all the congregation of the children of Israel. And thou shalt say to them: Be ye holy, because I the Lord your God am holy.
11. You shall not steal. You shall not lie: neither shall any man deceive his neighbour.
12. Thou shalt not swear falsely by my name, nor profane the name of thy God. I am the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 6:1-6</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/hosea6_1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 20:27:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/hosea6_1-6/</guid>
      <description>1 Come, and let us return unto the LORD: for he hath torn, and he will heal us; he hath smitten, and he will bind us up.
2 After two days will he revive us: in the third day he will raise us up, and we shall live in his sight.
3 Then shall we know, if we follow on to know the LORD: his going forth is prepared as the morning; and he shall come unto us as the rain, as the latter and former rain unto the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea 14:2-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/hosea14_2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:15:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/hosea14_2-10/</guid>
      <description>2 Take with you words, and turn to the LORD: say unto him, Take away all iniquity, and receive us graciously: so will we render the calves of our lips.
3 Asshur shall not save us; we will not ride upon horses: neither will we say any more to the work of our hands, Ye are our gods: for in thee the fatherless findeth mercy.
4 I will heal their backsliding, I will love them freely: for mine anger is turned away from him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 7:23-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</guid>
      <description>23 But this thing commanded I them, saying, Obey my voice, and I will be your God, and ye shall be my people: and walk ye in all the ways that I have commanded you, that it may be well unto you. 24 But they hearkened not, nor inclined their ear, but walked in the counsels and in the imagination of their evil heart, and went backward, and not forward. 25 Since the day that your fathers came forth out of the land of Egypt unto this day I have even sent unto you all my servants the prophets, daily rising up early and sending them: 26 Yet they hearkened not unto me, nor inclined their ear, but hardened their neck: they did worse than their fathers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 4:1,5-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:16:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy4_1_5-9/</guid>
      <description>1 Now therefore hearken, O Israel, unto the statutes and unto the judgments, which I teach you, for to do them, that ye may live, and go in and possess the land which the LORD God of your fathers giveth you.
5 Behold, I have taught you statutes and judgments, even as the LORD my God commanded me, that ye should do so in the land whither ye go to possess it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel 3:25,34-43</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</guid>
      <description>25 He answered and said, Lo, I see four men loose, walking in the midst of the fire, and they have no hurt; and the form of the fourth is like the Son of God【9†source】.
34 And at the end of the days I Nebuchadnezzar lifted up mine eyes unto heaven, and mine understanding returned unto me, and I blessed the most High, and I praised and honoured him that liveth for ever, whose dominion is an everlasting dominion, and his kingdom is from generation to generation: 35 And all the inhabitants of the earth are reputed as nothing: and he doeth according to his will in the army of heaven, and among the inhabitants of the earth: and none can stay his hand, or say unto him, What doest thou?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings 5:1-15</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/2kings5_1-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/2kings5_1-15/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Naaman, captain of the host of the king of Syria, was a great man with his master, and honourable, because by him the LORD had given deliverance unto Syria: he was also a mighty man in valour, but he was a leper.
2 And the Syrians had gone out by companies, and had brought away captive out of the land of Israel a little maid; and she waited on Naaman’s wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus 20:1-3,7-8,12-17</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:58:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/exodus20_1-3_7-8_12-17/</guid>
      <description>1 And God spake all these words, saying, 2 I am the LORD thy God, which have brought thee out of the land of Egypt, out of the house of bondage. 3 Thou shalt have no other gods before me.
7 Thou shalt not take the name of the LORD thy God in vain; for the LORD will not hold him guiltless that taketh his name in vain. 8 Remember the sabbath day, to keep it holy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah 7:14-15, 18-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:16:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</guid>
      <description>14 Feed thy people with thy rod, the flock of thine heritage, which dwell solitarily in the wood, in the midst of Carmel: let them feed in Bashan and Gilead, as in the days of old. 15 According to the days of thy coming out of the land of Egypt will I shew unto him marvellous things.
18 Who is a God like unto thee, that pardoneth iniquity, and passeth by the transgression of the remnant of his heritage?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 37:3-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/genesis37_3-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/genesis37_3-28/</guid>
      <description>3 Now Israel loved Joseph more than all his children, because he was the son of his old age: and he made him a coat of many colours. 4 And when his brethren saw that their father loved him more than all his brethren, they hated him, and could not speak peaceably unto him.
12 And his brethren went to feed their father’s flock in Shechem. 13a And Israel said unto Joseph, Do not thy brethren feed the flock in Shechem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah17_5 10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:48:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</guid>
      <description>5 Thus saith the LORD; Cursed be the man that trusteth in man, and maketh flesh his arm, and whose heart departeth from the LORD.
6 For he shall be like the heath in the desert, and shall not see when good cometh; but shall inhabit the parched places in the wilderness, in a salt land and not inhabited.
7 Blessed is the man that trusteth in the LORD, and whose hope the LORD is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah_18_18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</guid>
      <description>18 Then said they, Come, and let us devise devices against Jeremiah; for the law shall not perish from the priest, nor counsel from the wise, nor the word from the prophet. Come, and let us smite him with the tongue, and let us not give heed to any of his words.
19 Give heed to me, O LORD, and hearken to the voice of them that contend with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 1:10,16-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</guid>
      <description>10 Hear the word of the LORD, ye rulers of Sodom; give ear unto the law of our God, ye people of Gomorrah.
16 Wash you, make you clean; put away the evil of your doings from before mine eyes; cease to do evil; 17 Learn to do well; seek judgment, relieve the oppressed, judge the fatherless, plead for the widow. 18 Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 9:4-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</guid>
      <description>4b &amp;ldquo;Speak not thou in thine heart, after that the LORD thy God hath cast them out from before thee, saying, For my righteousness the LORD hath brought me in to possess this land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD doth drive them out from before thee.
5 Not for thy righteousness, or for the uprightness of thine heart, dost thou go to possess their land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD thy God doth drive them out from before thee, and that he may perform the word which the LORD sware unto thy fathers, Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said unto him, Abraham: and he said, Behold, here I am.
2 And he said, Take now thy son, thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and get thee into the land of Moriah; and offer him there for a burnt offering upon one of the mountains which I will tell thee of.
9 And they came to the place which God had told him of; and Abraham built an altar there, and laid the wood in order, and bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the altar upon the wood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 26:16-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:36:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</guid>
      <description>16 This day the LORD thy God hath commanded thee to do these statutes and judgments: thou shalt therefore keep and do them with all thine heart, and with all thy soul.
17 Thou hast avouched the LORD this day to be thy God, and to walk in his ways, and to keep his statutes, and his commandments, and his judgments, and to hearken unto his voice:
18 And the LORD hath avouched thee this day to be his peculiar people, as he hath promised thee, and that thou shouldest keep all his commandments;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>21 But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.
22 All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.
23 Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
