<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/ot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OT on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:16:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/ot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Micah 7:14-15, 18-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:16:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/micah7_14-15_18-20/</guid>
      <description>14 Feed thy people with thy rod, the flock of thine heritage, which dwell solitarily in the wood, in the midst of Carmel: let them feed in Bashan and Gilead, as in the days of old. 15 According to the days of thy coming out of the land of Egypt will I shew unto him marvellous things.
18 Who is a God like unto thee, that pardoneth iniquity, and passeth by the transgression of the remnant of his heritage?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 37:3-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/genesis37_3-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/genesis37_3-28/</guid>
      <description>3 Now Israel loved Joseph more than all his children, because he was the son of his old age: and he made him a coat of many colours. 4 And when his brethren saw that their father loved him more than all his brethren, they hated him, and could not speak peaceably unto him.
12 And his brethren went to feed their father’s flock in Shechem. 13a And Israel said unto Joseph, Do not thy brethren feed the flock in Shechem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah17_5 10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:48:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</guid>
      <description>5 Thus saith the LORD; Cursed be the man that trusteth in man, and maketh flesh his arm, and whose heart departeth from the LORD.
6 For he shall be like the heath in the desert, and shall not see when good cometh; but shall inhabit the parched places in the wilderness, in a salt land and not inhabited.
7 Blessed is the man that trusteth in the LORD, and whose hope the LORD is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah_18_18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</guid>
      <description>18 Then said they, Come, and let us devise devices against Jeremiah; for the law shall not perish from the priest, nor counsel from the wise, nor the word from the prophet. Come, and let us smite him with the tongue, and let us not give heed to any of his words.
19 Give heed to me, O LORD, and hearken to the voice of them that contend with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah 1:10,16-20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/isaiah1_10_16-20/</guid>
      <description>10 Hear the word of the LORD, ye rulers of Sodom; give ear unto the law of our God, ye people of Gomorrah.
16 Wash you, make you clean; put away the evil of your doings from before mine eyes; cease to do evil; 17 Learn to do well; seek judgment, relieve the oppressed, judge the fatherless, plead for the widow. 18 Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 9:4-10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:27:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy9_4-10/</guid>
      <description>4b &amp;ldquo;Speak not thou in thine heart, after that the LORD thy God hath cast them out from before thee, saying, For my righteousness the LORD hath brought me in to possess this land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD doth drive them out from before thee.
5 Not for thy righteousness, or for the uprightness of thine heart, dost thou go to possess their land: but for the wickedness of these nations the LORD thy God doth drive them out from before thee, and that he may perform the word which the LORD sware unto thy fathers, Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis 22:1-18</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:55:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/gen22_1-18/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass after these things, that God did tempt Abraham, and said unto him, Abraham: and he said, Behold, here I am.
2 And he said, Take now thy son, thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest, and get thee into the land of Moriah; and offer him there for a burnt offering upon one of the mountains which I will tell thee of.
9 And they came to the place which God had told him of; and Abraham built an altar there, and laid the wood in order, and bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the altar upon the wood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy 26:16-9</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:36:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/deuteronomy26_16-19/</guid>
      <description>16 This day the LORD thy God hath commanded thee to do these statutes and judgments: thou shalt therefore keep and do them with all thine heart, and with all thy soul.
17 Thou hast avouched the LORD this day to be thy God, and to walk in his ways, and to keep his statutes, and his commandments, and his judgments, and to hearken unto his voice:
18 And the LORD hath avouched thee this day to be his peculiar people, as he hath promised thee, and that thou shouldest keep all his commandments;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel 18:21-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:32:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/ezekiel-18_21-28/</guid>
      <description>21 But if the wicked will turn from all his sins that he hath committed, and keep all my statutes, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall surely live, he shall not die.
22 All his transgressions that he hath committed, they shall not be mentioned unto him: in his righteousness that he hath done he shall live.
23 Have I any pleasure at all that the wicked should die?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
