<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeremiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.art/tags/jeremiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jeremiah on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:24:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://matthew419.art/tags/jeremiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 20:10-13</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah20_10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:24:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah20_10-13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; For I heard the reproaches of many, and terror on every side: Persecute him, and let us persecute him: from all the men that were my familiars, and continued at my side: if by any means he may be deceived, and we may prevail against him, and be revenged on him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But the Lord is with me as a strong warrior: therefore they that persecute me shall fall, and shall be weak: they shall be greatly confounded, because they have not understood the everlasting reproach, which never shall be effaced.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And thou, O Lord of hosts, prover of the just, who seest the reins and the heart: let me see, I beseech thee, thy vengeance on them: for to thee I have laid open my cause.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Sing ye to the Lord, praise the Lord: because he hath delivered the soul of the poor out of the hand of the wicked .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 11:18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah11_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:26:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah11_18-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading&#34;&gt;Reading&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; And the Lord hath given me knowledge of it, and I know it: then thou showedst me their doings.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; But I was like a meek lamb that is carried to be sacrificed: and I knew not that they had devised devices against me, saying: Let us put wood in his bread, and cut him off from the land of the living, and let his name be remembered no more.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; But, O Lord of hosts, that judgest righteously, that triest the reins and the hearts, let me see thy vengeance on them: for to thee have I revealed my cause.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah 7:23-28</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah7_23-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; But this thing commanded I them, saying, Obey my voice, and I will be your God, and ye shall be my people: and walk ye in all the ways that I have commanded you, that it may be well unto you.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; But they hearkened not, nor inclined their ear, but walked in the counsels and in the imagination of their evil heart, and went backward, and not forward.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; Since the day that your fathers came forth out of the land of Egypt unto this day I have even sent unto you all my servants the prophets, daily rising up early and sending them:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; Yet they hearkened not unto me, nor inclined their ear, but hardened their neck: they did worse than their fathers.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore thou shalt speak all these words unto them; but they will not hearken to thee: thou shalt also call unto them; but they will not answer thee.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; But thou shalt say unto them, This is a nation that obeyeth not the voice of the LORD their God, nor receiveth correction: truth is perished, and is cut off from their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah17_5 10</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:48:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah17_5-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; Thus saith the LORD; Cursed be the man that trusteth in man, and maketh flesh his arm, and whose heart departeth from the LORD.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; For he shall be like the heath in the desert, and shall not see when good cometh; but shall inhabit the parched places in the wilderness, in a salt land and not inhabited.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; Blessed is the man that trusteth in the LORD, and whose hope the LORD is.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; For he shall be as a tree planted by the waters, and that spreadeth out her roots by the river, and shall not see when heat cometh, but her leaf shall be green; and shall not be careful in the year of drought, neither shall cease from yielding fruit.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; The heart is deceitful above all things, and desperately wicked: who can know it?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; I the LORD search the heart, I try the reins, even to give every man according to his ways, and according to the fruit of his doings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah_18_18 20</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew419.art/post/jeremiah_18_18-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Then said they, Come, and let us devise devices against Jeremiah; for the law shall not perish from the priest, nor counsel from the wise, nor the word from the prophet. Come, and let us smite him with the tongue, and let us not give heed to any of his words.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Give heed to me, O LORD, and hearken to the voice of them that contend with me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
