<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>https://matthew419.me/tags/daniel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Daniel on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:33:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthew419.me/tags/daniel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daniel3_14 20_91 92_95</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel3_14-20_91-92_95/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:33:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel3_14-20_91-92_95/</guid>
      <description>Reading 14 Nebuchadnezzar addressing them, said: Is it true, O Sidrach, Misach, and Abdenago, that you do not worship my gods, nor adore the golden statue that I have set up? 15 Now therefore if you be ready, at what hour soever you shall hear the sound of the trumpet, flute, harp, sackbut, psaltery, and symphony, and of all kinds of music, prostrate yourselves, and adore the statue that I have made: but if you do not adore, you shall be cast the same hour into the furnace of burning fire: and who is the God that shall deliver you out of my hand?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel 13:1-9,5-17, 19-30, 33-62</title>
      <link>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel13_1-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:55:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthew419.me/post/daniel13_1-9/</guid>
      <description>Reading 1 In Babylon there lived a man named Joakim, 2 who married a woman named Susanna, the daughter of Hilkiah, a very beautiful woman and one who feared the Lord. 3 Her parents were righteous and had instructed their daughter according to the law of Moses. 4 Joakim was very rich; he had a garden near his house, and the Jews came to him because he was the most honored of them all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
