<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OT  on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ot-/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OT  on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:16:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/ot-/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daniel 3:25,34-43</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 04:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/daniel3_25_34-43/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; He answered and said, Lo, I see four men loose, walking in the midst of the fire, and they have no hurt; and the form of the fourth is like the Son of God【9†source】.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; And at the end of the days I Nebuchadnezzar lifted up mine eyes unto heaven, and mine understanding returned unto me, and I blessed the most High, and I praised and honoured him that liveth for ever, whose dominion is an everlasting dominion, and his kingdom is from generation to generation:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And all the inhabitants of the earth are reputed as nothing: and he doeth according to his will in the army of heaven, and among the inhabitants of the earth: and none can stay his hand, or say unto him, What doest thou?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; At the same time my reason returned unto me; and for the glory of my kingdom, mine honour and brightness returned unto me; and my counsellors and my lords sought unto me; and I was established in my kingdom, and excellent majesty was added unto me.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; Now I Nebuchadnezzar praise and extol and honour the King of heaven, all whose works are truth, and his ways judgment: and those that walk in pride he is able to abase.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
