<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthew on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/matthew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Matthew on Follow me and I shall make you fishers of men.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:55:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/matthew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 25:31-46</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew25_31-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:55:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew25_31-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matthew 25:31-46&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;31.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;When the Son of man shall come in his majesty, and all the angels with him, then shall he sit upon the seat of his majesty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32.&lt;/strong&gt; And all nations shall be gathered together before him: and he shall separate them one from another, as the shepherd separateth the sheep from the goats:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33.&lt;/strong&gt; And he shall set the sheep on his right hand, but the goats on his left.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:17-19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_17-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:17:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_17-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; Think not that I am come to destroy the law, or the prophets: I am not come to destroy, but to fulfil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; For verily I say unto you, Till heaven and earth pass, one jot or one tittle shall in no wise pass from the law, till all be fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; Whosoever therefore shall break one of these least commandments, and shall teach men so, he shall be called the least in the kingdom of heaven: but whosoever shall do and teach them, the same shall be called great in the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 21:33-46</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew21_33-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 12:02:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew21_33-46/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;33&lt;/strong&gt; Hear another parable: There was a certain householder, which planted a vineyard, and hedged it round about, and digged a winepress in it, and built a tower, and let it out to husbandmen, and went into a far country:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; And when the time of the fruit drew near, he sent his servants to the husbandmen, that they might receive the fruits of it.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;35&lt;/strong&gt; And the husbandmen took his servants, and beat one, and killed another, and stoned another.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt; Again, he sent other servants more than the first: and they did unto them likewise.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;37&lt;/strong&gt; But last of all he sent unto them his son, saying, They will reverence my son.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt; But when the husbandmen saw the son, they said among themselves, This is the heir; come, let us kill him, and let us seize on his inheritance.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt; And they caught him, and cast him out of the vineyard, and slew him.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt; When the lord therefore of the vineyard cometh, what will he do unto those husbandmen?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;41&lt;/strong&gt; They say unto him, He will miserably destroy those wicked men, and will let out his vineyard unto other husbandmen, which shall render him the fruits in their seasons.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;42&lt;/strong&gt; Jesus saith unto them, Did ye never read in the scriptures, The stone which the builders rejected, the same is become the head of the corner: this is the Lord’s doing, and it is marvellous in our eyes?&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore say I unto you, The kingdom of God shall be taken from you, and given to a nation bringing forth the fruits thereof.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 20:17-28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew20_17-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew20_17-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt; And Jesus going up to Jerusalem took the twelve disciples apart in the way, and said unto them,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;18&lt;/strong&gt; Behold, we go up to Jerusalem; and the Son of man shall be betrayed unto the chief priests and unto the scribes, and they shall condemn him to death,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt; And shall deliver him to the Gentiles to mock, and to scourge, and to crucify him: and the third day he shall rise again.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; Then came to him the mother of Zebedee&amp;rsquo;s children with her sons, worshipping him, and desiring a certain thing of him.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; And he said unto her, What wilt thou? She saith unto him, Grant that these my two sons may sit, the one on thy right hand, and the other on the left, in thy kingdom.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus answered and said, Ye know not what ye ask. Are ye able to drink of the cup that I shall drink of, and to be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with? They say unto him, We are able.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt; And he saith unto them, Ye shall drink indeed of my cup, and be baptized with the baptism that I am baptized with: but to sit on my right hand, and on my left, is not mine to give, but it shall be given to them for whom it is prepared of my Father.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;24&lt;/strong&gt; And when the ten heard it, they were moved with indignation against the two brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt; But Jesus called them unto him, and said, Ye know that the princes of the Gentiles exercise dominion over them, and they that are great exercise authority upon them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; But it shall not be so among you: but whosoever will be great among you, let him be your minister;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;27&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever will be chief among you, let him be your servant:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;28&lt;/strong&gt; Even as the Son of man came not to be ministered unto, but to minister, and to give his life a ransom for many.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23:1-12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew23_1-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:19:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew23_1-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Then spake Jesus to the multitude, and to his disciples,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; Saying, The scribes and the Pharisees sit in Moses&amp;rsquo; seat:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; All therefore whatsoever they bid you observe, that observe and do; but do not ye after their works: for they say, and do not.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt; For they bind heavy burdens and grievous to be borne, and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; But all their works they do for to be seen of men: they make broad their phylacteries, and enlarge the borders of their garments,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt; And love the uppermost rooms at feasts, and the chief seats in the synagogues,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt; And greetings in the markets, and to be called of men, Rabbi, Rabbi.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt; But be not ye called Rabbi: for one is your Master, even Christ; and all ye are brethren.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt; And call no man your father upon the earth: for one is your Father, which is in heaven.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt; Neither be ye called masters: for one is your Master, even Christ.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;11&lt;/strong&gt; But he that is greatest among you shall be your servant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt; And whosoever shall exalt himself shall be abased; and he that shall humble himself shall be exalted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:43-48</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_43-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 04:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_43-48/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;43&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it hath been said, Thou shalt love thy neighbour, and hate thine enemy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;44&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;45&lt;/strong&gt; That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 5:20-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_20-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/matthew5_20-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;20&lt;/strong&gt; For I say unto you, That except your righteousness shall exceed the righteousness of the scribes and Pharisees, ye shall in no case enter into the kingdom of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt; Ye have heard that it was said by them of old time, Thou shalt not kill; and whosoever shall kill shall be in danger of the judgment: &lt;strong&gt;22&lt;/strong&gt; But I say unto you, That whosoever is angry with his brother without a cause shall be in danger of the judgment: and whosoever shall say to his brother, Raca, shall be in danger of the council: but whosoever shall say, Thou fool, shall be in danger of hell fire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
